(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
On September 26,
the second Last Stage: 24H was revealed.
The four directors who lost the matchup...
are on the Last Stage for survival.
Only 24 hours are given...
to four directors.
And 20 cubes.
(What am I supposed to do?)
(This is crazy.)
(I can't create any choreography.)
(Mental breakdown)
(I was completely clueless.)
(There was no guideline or whatsoever.)
(I'll just go home.)
(There's nothing I can do with these.)
They had to interpret 20 cubes in their own ways...
and presented completely different performances.
(If I try to die, I'll live.)
(If I try to live, I'll die.)
(I'm going to try to die. That's my attitude.)
(It was a matter of survival.)
(I'll pull it off and never go home.)
(I must...)
(win again.)
(Just send anyone among the other three.)
(I don't care as long as it's not me.)
Director NaiN completed an energetic performance...
by making versatile use of the cubes.
Director BABYZOO put on a powerful performance...
by emphasizing his main genre, waacking.
Director JEONG MIN JUN created three-dimensional scenes...
by making harmony between the cubes and the dancers.
(Exclaiming)
By using the laser...
and throwing the cubes,
Director Kasper created an intense performance.
After holding a survival competition...
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(The second Last Stage: 24H)
(NaiN and BABYZOO met as the final elimination candidates.)
(NaiN is eliminated.)
(Eliminated choreographer: NaiN)
(In the second Last Stage: 24H, NaiN is eliminated.)
(Oh, NaiN.)
(This resulted...)
(from what we focused on in the evaluation.)
(This never means you were incapable as a director.)
(NaiN put on a cool, happy performance before she left.)
(That's what I wanted to tell you.)
(Thank you.)
(Good job. You did well.)
(NaiN's journey ends here.)
(You can watch Last Stage: 24H on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
(After another Last Stage ends...)
(Sighing)
(Entering her Director's Room for the last time)
Goodbye.
I'll have to take this back home.
(Let me decorate my room.)
(Ta-da!)
(This is the "Street Dance Girls Fighter" winner trophy.)
(She decorated her Director's Room herself.)
NaiN.
A letter for me? I should be the one writing to you.
Why? NaiN.
I feel so bad.
If only I had done better,
- this wouldn't have happened.
- Don't say that.
That's how I feel.
I have to face it.
One thing is clear.
Everything you've done here...
was awesome.
Really? Thank you.
It's a present for you.
- It's a kind of souvenir.
- Really? This is cute.
(During the Title Sequence Film Mission)
Your phone case is yellow.
Yes. I like yellow.
- My nails too.
- Your nails are yellow too.
(He heard NaiN loves yellow by chance.)
Since you like yellow.
This is all I can do for you.
I can't write a letter.
I don't know how to.
Thank you so much.
Take it with you everywhere.
Thank you.
Well done.
- Thank you.
- You were amazing.
(The choreographers deliver their hearts in their own ways.)
What Street World Fighter: Directors' War means to me?
It was a turning point in my life.
A turning point as I enter my mid-20s.
Wait a minute. What is this?
I'm here with the name NaiN.
(She joined as Nain, not as a team.)
I've never done anything half-heartedly even for a moment.
(NaiN did her best every time.)
I gave it my all, without any regrets.
I'm proud of myself.
I was highly inspired and touched...
by the fellow directors.
It gave me a chance to grow a lot.
I can't wait to see...
how much my life's going to change...
when I apply what I learned from this experience to my life.
That will become...
a huge turning point in my life.
I had a great time.
(NaiN leaves her Director's Room after showing her passion.)
Cool. Nice view here.
(Kasper and MIN JUN receive a strange envelope.)
Is it another mission?
- I've never had that before.
- What's that?
"Kasper and JEONG MIN JUN came back alive."
"Can you survive from 184m above ground?"
(Kasper is afraid of heights.)
For real?
(The highest in the world registered in the Guinness World Records)
(Sky bridge observatory)
(The extreme edge walk experience 184m above the ground)
(Special training for the Last Stage survivals)
(Entering after getting ready)
(Groaning)
(Everywhere...)
(they look, )
(the 184m high observatory is brutal.)
Are we really doing this?
(Putting on the safety gear)
(It was safely filmed in the company of the professionals.)
Once we're out there,
we can't come back.
(Help me.)
(Moving to the railing to try it)
This is already so scary.
(The view from 184m above the ground before their eyes)
It's so windy.
(He's just brave.)
(This is where MIN JUN is standing.)
(The boy born in 2004 is walking without crying.)
(Laidback)
(The boy born in 1992 is about to cry.)
(He stays close to the wall and is barely moving.)
MIN JUN, you're amazing.
No wonder you survived two Last Stages.
I should be registered in the world records.
You should be.
This is really scary.
(What JEONG MIN JUN and Kasper are seeing)
I'll explain what you're going to do now.
You'll stand at the edge of the railing...
with your heels out.
(Horrified)
Push your body and lean back.
While doing that...
(They have to get their hands off the rope.)
(Dizzy)
Wait.
Do I really have to do this?
I can't do it.
Walk forward and line up with me.
(Accepting his fate calmly)
(Marching)
(In denial)
I can't do this.
(A terrifying view before his eyes)
(Holding tight)
Walk forward like me.
(Plucking up his courage to step forward)
(Finally taking a step forward)
(Taking another step)
(Just one more step!)
(You can do it, Kasper.)
(Marching toward the sea bravely)
Good. Now, you're going to turn...
and face the cameramen.
(Another crisis)
(Groaning)
I feel miserable.
(Drooping)
Wait. This is too...
Straighten your knees and lean.
- Good.
- You're amazing.
(Waving his hands)
Good.
(How can he do that?)
(Kasper begins bending his knees.)
(Losing his mind)
Straighten your knees and lean.
Straighten them.
Good.
I'll hold the rope.
Let your hands go.
Now, open your arm.
- Gosh.
- It's okay. I got it.
Good.
Wait.
(Kasper and MIN JUN succeed in leaning 184m above the ground.)
That's good.
(A photo to prove their survival 184m above the ground)
(Trembling)
(Another pose from BAILEY's choreography)
(The two made dizzying memories.)
(Returning after taking pictures)
(Stunned)
(Since when were we this close?)
(Kasper freezes.)
- Good job.
- You did it.
(The two overcame their fears and pulled off a major challenge.)
That relieved the frustration inside.
I'll pull off the next mission,
so I can win.
That gave me confidence.
I'm going to work even harder.
No more!
Last Stage!
Send everyone who ends up in the Last Stage.
I'll pay for it.
("Royalty" by Yoon Mi Rae and Tiger JK)
(Directed by Back Koo Young)
(To be continued)
(The super kids direction mission went viral after it was revealed.)
(From idols to kids?)
(The man with parenting experience)
(Out of my way!)
(Devil in you)
(It's funny how they can't control kids.)
(That's hilarious.)
(Giving up)
(Simeez and BABYZOO have lost it.)
(Why do you keep looking at the ground?)
(Flustered)
(It's funny how he can't talk back and bites his lip.)
(A kids battle?)
(Super kids are here to turn the square upside down.)
(Excited)
(They're so cute.)
(I don't know where to look.)
(The Super Kids Dancer Casting Battle begins.)
(Super class beyond imagination)
(Thrilled)
(He's like Bruce Lee.)
(A series of marvelous dancing that stuns the grown-ups)
(How can he be so flexible?)
(Look at his moves. That's crazy.)
(Kids continue to give them a heart attack.)
(Throbbing)
(I'm in love.)
(Kids dancer casting meeting)
(The 4-people team takes a long time to decide.)
(What's good about having 4 people in the team is...)
(that we get one more idea.)
(What's bad is...)
(there's another opinion.)
(Why is it so hard to come to an agreement?)
(We're having a hard time uniting.)
(It's called a team match, but it's basically an individual match.)
(Super Kids Direct Mission was even harder...)
(because it was their first time.)
(That's awesome!)
(I think they're going to win.)
(It's about time to surprise people.)
(That's what I'm talking about.)
(See? I had to surprise them.)
(Who will enter the semifinal...)
(and who will head to the Last Stage?)
(That broke my heart big time.)
(You can watch Last Stage: 24H on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
- Hello.
I'm back to the battlefield.
(Back to the Director's Room)
It's been a while.
I'm already back for the next mission.
Time really flies.
I've been trying to recover...
and pull off my schedule.
I joined as a judge.
There were many kid dancers.
They were around 13 or 14.
I want to teach them.
Every student from my academy...
will be known as incredible dancers.
I'd be happy.
I didn't think you'd like kids.
I don't.
My nephew is so cute. I miss him already.
What are we doing?
I was planning to stay calm, but I'm startled again.
(No!)
Finally. Here it comes.
Let's go.
I haven't heard the siren in a while.
(What's the next mission at the fourth crossroads of fate?)
(All 7 choreographers are seated.)
Seven choreographers...
competed for their reputation.
They'll compete once again to prove their directing skills.
The next mission will be their new challenge.
Just thinking about it terrifies me.
It was totally unpredictable.
I was anxious.
Here it is.
What's it going to be?
I couldn't predict what the mission was going to be.
The mega crew mission for sure.
- My heart is in pain.
- Hello.
- What?
- My heart is in pain.
- Hello.
- What's that?
Hello. I'm ShiN from Japan.
I'm 12 years old.
- Hello.
- What's going on?
- What? Are we working with kids?
- I'm not sure about this.
We're dancers from Japan.
- We're dancers.
- Kid dancers?
- It's a kids mega crew mission.
I was dumbfounded. I was like, "What's happening?"
I'm Third Bro, a b-boy from China.
I'm Song Haoming from China.
- He's cute.
- My name is s, o, So.
Chinese dancers are amazing.
I'm Jack.B. I'm 13.
It's Jack.B.
I know them. They were in my class.
- No way.
- I was becoming more certain.
Those who will join the directors for this mission are...
Us, global kid dancers.
Gosh.
(Getting up)
I'm shocked.
I never saw that coming.
(Losing her mind)
This mission is...
the Super Kids Direct Mission.
Direct the Next Generation.
- Really?
- You're lying.
I'm directing a super kid every day.
- Right.
- Last night,
this morning. Every single day.
You're giving a kids direct mission...
when I'm directing a kid every day?
I thought it was a prank.
I've never seen this anywhere before.
I never saw that coming.
It's the first time...
in the history of this series.
I surrender.
It's funny though.
Because they're still growing,
kid dancers have infinite potential.
You'll go beyond judging their current level...
and discover their unique strengths...
and potential.
You'll guide them to bring out their potential...
and capture it all on film.
You'll face who you truly are.
Stress and patience.
That's going to be the tough part.
I wonder if the other choreographers understand how hard it is.
I'm devastated.
I'm not sure I can meet them at their level.
Simeez might struggle with it.
She has no intention of meeting them at their level.
I teach pretty fast.
"Are you ready to do this together?"
I can't do that.
This isn't going to be easy.
Wait!
Kids. Wait.
(Simeez having a mental breakdown is coming soon.)
I'm actually worried about Kasper.
I love this mission.
I've always wanted to teach kids.
I'm intrigued by it.
(Father Kasper is coming soon.)
The one who's going to be best at it?
Either BADA or BABYZOO.
BABYZOO looks like he'd be good at it.
"Guys, let's go."
"Again."
"Guys, do you want to do this 100 times?"
(Again)
(BABYZOO the clear-eyed maniac is coming soon.)
I'm experienced.
I taught elementary school boys...
for two years.
That's amazing experience.
I know what they like.
I know when they lose focus.
I think those memories will help me.
You look like you'll be good at it.
They probably know BADA.
Regardless, being experienced...
makes a big difference.
My strength is...
the memories of my youth that I still have.
Hey, we have them too.
We still have them too.
I remember them too!
(The young boy is flustered.)
- I remember them too!
- He often says that.
I can't imagine MIN JUN directing them.
I don't know if kids will be able to pull off MIN JUN's style.
It's up to MIN JUN to lead kids to pull it off.
This mission will be...
There's an odd number of us.
So I'm expecting an individual match.
The Super Kids Direct Mission...
will be a team match.
- I knew it.
- What?
Yay.
I'm not good with kids.
I thought we could help each other out.
I'd happy to work with anyone.
I'm not exactly into a team match.
Everyone has different perspectives and opinions.
We might not agree. We might not get along.
It might be difficult for us to reach an agreement.
But there are seven of us.
How are we going to form teams?
The teams will be decided...
What is it?
based on the concept paper you wrote.
What?
What does that mean?
You'll move to your Director's Room...
and complete the concept paper.
The best masterpiece is the story.
I'm afraid my concept and story might be a bit childish.
What should I do?
Oh, my gosh. What am I going to do with the kids?
(7 choreographers complete the concept paper.)
I wondered how teams were divided...
based on the concept paper.
By presenting it?
Each choreographer will receive...
six concept papers without the names excluding your own.
Solely based on the concept paper,
pick top two concepts...
that are expected to be the best.
It was important.
Judging by the concept? That's fair.
After everyone makes their choices,
the writer of the most chosen concept paper...
will decide the team.
(Unbelievable)
This time...
I want to decide on my own team.
I love power.
I did think that it would be great to be able to decide.
The team decider will decide whether to finish the piece...
as a 3-man team or 4-man team.
Without knowing who the writer is,
the concepts will be chosen...
to form the team.
The remaining choreographers...
will automatically be formed as the opposing team.
Being able to choose my own team...
means a dream team can be formed...
when there are good concepts.
I can't be sure if it's someone I wish to work with...
since the names won't be revealed.
I thought that my concept was quite obvious.
I think I can figure out the other concepts as well.
Based on the number of team members,
each team will split their piece into chapters.
Each choreographer must be in charge of each chapter...
and take care of the concept, music, choreography, and directing.
Each chapter must be at least 40 seconds.
- I see.
While putting together a piece as a team,
each person will be evaluated personally...
as a director of each chapter.
It's a team battle, but we're all against each other.
It's one piece,
but there has to be something that stands out.
It has to be tasty.
There should be an impact when my chapter plays.
This mission...
will be evaluated by the Fight Judges.
The choreographers on the same team...
will earn the same team score.
The team score and personal score will be added together...
to become the final score.
Based on these scores,
the personal ranks will be decided from 1st place to 7th place.
The personal scores will have a greater significance...
that the team scores.
Gosh, that's harsh.
It's an individual game pretending to be a team game.
The team scores are less significant than the individual scores.
It means the focus is on the individual in the end.
It's still important to meet good team members.
There's a big disadvantage if the team fails to win.
Winning is a must.
The choreographer...
who fails to prove their directing skills in this mission...
will have to prove their will to survive...
by entering Last Stage: 24H.
I tried not to be afraid of it.
But I think I'm afraid of it.
I didn't want to be there.
I don't want to be there.
The number of choreographers who will head to Last Stage: 24H...
- How many will it be?
- Two?
Three?
is four.
(Last Stage: 24H)
- What?
It's the rest except for three?
Only three will survive? That's a low chance.
(Shocked)
If it's more than half out of seven,
it can always be me.
I've already been there once. Even if I do end up there...
I never want to be there! Never!
I'm in danger.
Shouldn't I be preparing for the Last Stage instead?
It was really harsh.
"No, BADA. You won't end up there."
Becoming the team decider will be very important.
Now, you must head over to your Directors' Rooms...
and choose two concept papers.
I can't wait to see what I'll find.
People will definitely like my concept.
I did think that my concept was the most intuitive and on point.
This is my cheat code.
"Being myself."
I came up with a good concept.
I had to decide on the 1st and 2nd priorities.
I thought about the standards I should base them on.
That was it?
It really threw me off.
This is driving me crazy.
Here they are.
(The anonymous concept papers were sent to each room.)
Everyone did a good job.
I didn't think this was this important.
The team selection is crucial.
I should've worked a bit harder.
We can't know the writers of the concept papers,
but we can understand the quality of the piece they wish to make.
I would've done a better job if I had known.
To be honest, I think the others will know it's me.
"Musicality."
(Musicality)
(Kapser's trait: He always talks about musicality.)
"Musicality."
The others are musical instruments...
and I'm the conductor who leads them.
This sounds like Kasper based on the title.
I think this one is Kasper's.
Kasper is the only one who wants to become a conductor.
He wants to form an orchestra?
It's so predictable.
"Musicality" seems to be Tae Woo's.
It's so predictable. I will put this one away.
This one is the longest. "Born to Be Stars."
"Born to Be Stars."
"Dancing like crazy." This phrase made it feel like...
it was BABYZOO's.
Just his name is missing. All of this is BABYZOO.
He's a born-to-be star.
It was based on my story.
While watching fancy dancers and celebrities on TV,
I developed an interest in dancing.
I wanted to share my story.
"After waking up from the dream, the dream is written on..."
I never do things like these.
This is what it's like.
Gosh!
(The child wakes up from his dream.)
My dream...
is to become a super dancer!
That's how it ends.
Gosh! I can't do this!
"Home."
It's based on war.
It wishes all children to be able to return home.
"Paradise." The background is an orphanage...
or a community of children.
This one is also a heavy topic.
The topics are heavier than I expected.
I wanted to talk about a child's experience.
"Do you want to go to the secret playground with me?"
It's a playground full of pure innocence.
Anyone has a sense of innocence inside of them.
I wanted to make people live through those moments...
through children.
My expressions might seem rough and sharp,
but I've always danced with an innocent heart.
I think everyone will enjoy the playground or hideout.
I don't want to go to the playground.
The location must be set for this one.
"School and uniform." I think I should avoid...
these one-dimensional words.
Hold on.
Isn't this too simple? "Friends."
"We become with the language of dancing..."
"even though we speak different languages."
This sounds like a campaign slogan.
instead of being a concept or story.
All right. The next one is "The Unknown World."
This one is hard to understand.
The story doesn't stand out.
It's too vague.
My top priority is "Friends."
My second priority is "The Unknown World."
It's the same for the other four.
If the focus is too strong on the message,
I feel like it will make us feel trapped.
I went for the simple ones.
I'll choose the playground one as my top priority.
I think it will be convenient to split it into chapters.
I want to work with BABYZOO.
Should I just pick "Born to Be Stars?"
I went with a deep concept as my top priority.
My second priority is a simple one.
I think "Born to Be Stars" will be easier to understand.
(The choreographers chose their priorities with their own plans.)
Which concept paper...
will get the most votes?
(Super Kids Direct Mission)
(Team decider, INGYOO)
(INGYOO placed 1st?)
It's INGYOO?
It's Choreographer INGYOO's piece,
"Do You Want to Go to the Secret Playground With Me?"
(It was INGYOO's!)
It was INGYOO's.
INGYOO is the team decider.
Please head to the Directors' Room...
and put together your team...
for the Super Kids Direct Mission.
That must be great.
Hold on! I don't know the owners of the concept papers anyway.
This is crazy.
He has to decide without knowing the names?
(The team decider is lost in thought.)
I want to work with MIN JUN this time.
MIN JUN always had a big impact...
when it came to storytelling.
I want to work with INGYOO.
You must be sick of INGYOO, Hee Jung.
You worked with him for the previous one.
It might feel predictable,
but working with Simeez will never go wrong.
I think BADA will do a tasty job with the group dance.
INGYOO should work with Kasper.
That will be fun to watch.
I didn't choose his concept.
I didn't go to the playground.
INGYOO and Kasper's clash chemistry?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
How am I supposed to decide just by these?
The way I see it, "Musicality,"
"Friends," and "The Unknown World..."
were written by simple people.
"Home," "Paradise," and "Born to Be Stars."
These people have solid storylines...
and can be writers.
In these team missions, writers are needed.
I'll go with these.
What kind of decision did INGYOO make?
I want to work with him.
I'm sure it won't be me.
(Super Kids Direct Mission: Team decider, INGYOO)
("Friends" is his first choice.)
It's "Friends." Who is this?
I'm not sure.
Who do you think it will be?
The content was too simple.
I couldn't tell who wrote this.
Doesn't it feel like BABYZOO's?
(Who is the owner of "Friends?")
("Friends" by BADA)
- Gosh!
It was BADA!
I didn't expect it to be her.
I felt happy because I chose INGYOO's.
We were able to choose each other.
Right.
(Good thing he didn't choose mine.)
Who else did he pick?
The next one.
("The Unknown World" by Simeez)
(He's satisfied again.)
(Screaming)
The team will become stable...
if there's someone I've worked with before.
Will you work as a three-person team...
or a four-person team?
I will...
not stop with forming my team.
- Yes!
- One more!
- That makes it more exciting.
- Yes!
I could've stopped there as I was satisfied with the members.
But I thought that there would be a better balance with another guy.
Those older girls are too strong.
I needed another member.
Please!
I hoped it was MIN JUN as I needed a storyteller.
I really wanted to work with INGYOO.
("Paradise")
What a relief.
(BABYZOO of "Born to Be Stars" is excluded.)
I have no idea who it is.
(Who is the owner of "Paradise" who will join INGYOO's team?)
("Paradise" by JEONG MIN JUN)
(Laughing)
(Smiling brightly)
I'm finally no longer the odd one out.
Nice. I was satisfied with the team.
We had the eyes of men and women.
I believe we can share many different tastes.
Right. The three of us are in a team.
We had an accumulated collection of data.
We have a good chance.
There are two boomers in the team.
"BABYZOO stuck in between the older ones."
I will support them well as the youngest one.
We have to go with a concept that's different from theirs.
I hope we can look like a team...
and make it look like one complete project.
We seem to be the ones with more stability.
The quality of the overall piece is important.
That's the best for the individuals.
I want us to work well as a team.
This kid has no talent.
The others are all great dancers.
But what this kid had...
was tenacity.
Being consistent is also a great talent.
The main character didn't have much talent.
I wanted to throw a message...
that being consistent is also a talent.
This is one of the evaluation categories.
"Did the star kid..."
"show the potential of the next dance generation?"
That topic...
fits perfectly with this category.
I wanted it to be a story that made sense...
as it was about kids.
As there was a slight connection with my concept,
I thought I could express it very well.
I want it to be bright.
I want to match their eye level...
and make something while hanging out with them.
How does the secret playground sound?
I have to be straightforward.
I must be a strong leader.
The tone that INGYOO had about what he was going to make...
was similar to the concept I came up with.
INGYOO's concept was distinct as his was chosen.
I tried to listen to his opinion as much as possible.
- Did you watch "Spider-Man?"
- The recent one?
I think that's a good idea.
The kids can wear masks.
They'll become great dancers whenever they put on the masks.
"Gosh!"
(Like this)
That's so cute.
That's so cute!
I liked the idea of the masks.
They believe the talent comes from the masks.
Right. That's how the story should go.
But all they did was to take out what was inside.
- But...
- Right.
- The mask gave them the courage.
- It's like how you wear sunglasses.
- Right.
The idea of shy kids discovering the masks.
The shy kids...
discover masks and put them on.
While fighting in a battle with confidence,
the masks come off.
The masks weren't the source of the superpowers.
All they needed was the courage to bring out their talents.
The penetrating message was really good.
I earned a sense of certainty.
- Hello.
Hello.
I want the music for Chapter 1 and Chapter 2...
- to be quite aggressive.
- Right.
It shouldn't just feel all happy.
In Chapter Three, there should be a bridge that dies down.
There should be a dramatic scene with a dance break.
The piano sound will...
- be in the background.
- Right.
Whether it's Chapter 2 or Chapter 3,
I wish for that sound to be in the background.
- As for Chapter Three, - Okay.
the song will build up with a lot more beats and choruses...
along with the sessions.
So ultimately, there are three chapters, right?
Right. We want the song to be one complete song.
One complete song...
- instead of three different songs?
- Right.
Things went smoothly.
I felt very relieved.
(The next day)
(Super Kids Dancer Casting)
- Hello.
Super Kids Dancer Casting!
I wonder how amazing they will be.
We have to do well with the casting...
for us to create the piece we wish to create.
Today is a very important day.
They were all great dancers in the clips.
That's my choreography!
He's nine!
- Gosh!
Right. These two are really famous.
(The 7 choreographers watched their videos.)
- They're so good!
- Gosh!
We'll be able to see how good they are today.
I wonder what they will make us do.
These people won't make us take turns to choose.
Will each team take turns to choose?
Or will it be a blind test?
Won't it be a battle?
It's a battle for the directors.
That would make me feel so happy.
I went into a head-to-ground position for Koo Young.
We won't be doing that, will we?
Please!
We have to get the one we want, no matter what.
Sugiura Shin.
She's a candidate...
of the main character.
- I think she can act as well.
- Right.
Shin...
was perfect as a main character candidate.
She's a classic afro dancer.
She was such a charming character.
In terms of talent,
Honatsu and Third Bro are at the top.
Shin is a great character.
I totally agree that Shin is great.
It's not about wanting to do the afro style to bring her.
Her dancing was on another level.
I didn't want to miss out on Shin.
I think Shin is our top priority and Honatsu is our second priority.
No individual decisions.
- No individual decisions.
- Okay.
We must discuss it before picking someone.
- Right.
- Setup!
- Rise!
- Twist!
- Resolve!
- Let's go!
During the 400 Mission,
I let Tae Woo take the dancer casting right...
and regretted it so much.
(Holding a grudge)
That can't happen again.
That really can't happen again.
I won't yield this time.
- We must sort it out carefully.
- Sounds good.
For a good piece,
there must be good cast members.
I wish for us to cast many of the dancers...
based on our initial plan.
Let's have a great time.
Come to my team.
(The siren goes off again at the Directors' Square.)
(In distress)
The time has come. Let's go.
Let's take a seat first.
I felt slightly worried.
I did pick out a few names.
Today is the day when I can't get them taken away.
It will be a tough battle.
There are parts that can begin when the casting is done.
Bringing the kid dancers is the most important part.
I won't get them taken away from me.
What's important about today's casting...
is that we need a main character.
Based on the talents of the main character...
the moves will feel different...
along with the expression.
We had to secure our target to make that happen.
Oh, my gosh.
Gosh, I feel so drained.
- Hello.
- What?
(Someone comes up on stage with a familiar voice.)
(Special MC Lip J returns.)
(Cheering)
You look amazing!
Currently, the 7 choreographers are split into 2 teams...
for the Super Kids Direct Mission.
One piece is created as a team,
but everyone's survival...
is decided based on each director's directing skills.
Thus, it's an individual battle.
The concept and direction of the piece has been decided...
and it was divided into different chapters.
Even the music has been produced.
What's left...
is to cast the kid dancers...
who will complete your pieces.
We all want similar names.
If I want to secure them,
I must be fully alert.
I'm trying to stay alert to be able to cast...
the right characters.
We definitely want the same names.
I'm sure there's going to be a bit of confusion.
It's going to make us sweat.
We were being careful at the start.
Making the best choice.
It requires a lot of thinking.
To cast the same dancer,
I believe there will be an intense competition.
It's time to witness with our own eyes...
the talent, charms, and potential of the kid dancers.
We'll witness them with our own eyes?
What's going on?
It could be different from the previous session.
I felt anxious.
For the Super Kids Dancer Casting,
there will be a Kids Battle.
- Kids Battle?
- What?
How exciting!
(This is so exciting!)
A dance battle?
(It's going to be exciting.)
Yes! I loved it.
While being able to witness the talents of these amazing kids,
it was exciting that it was in the form of a show.
Starting now,
Oh, yes!
"Starting now!"
the Super Kids Dancer Casting...
will begin!
(Super Kids Dancer Casting)
(Come on, babies!)
- Let's go!
- Are they entering?
- Here they are!
(Excited)
(What's going on?)
(The global kid dancers march forward.)
Gosh, they're so cute!
(The adults get excited after seeing the super kids.)
They're so cute!
(Startled)
This is insane.
Check out his character!
I can see it!
Gosh, they're so cute!
Let's go!
(Grooving to the max)
This kid was insane.
(Dancing-holic)
Gosh, they're so good!
It gave me goosebumps.
I felt a burst of dopamine.
Gosh, they're so small.
They're babies!
Gosh, they're so cute!
(The Directors' Square is high on the happy virus.)
(This is it!)
(The place is filled with proud smiles.)
I felt so happy at that moment.
Gosh, they're so cute!
Kids smaller than me came out...
and went, "Look at me!"
They were making themselves known through their dancing.
(Screaming)
It was so impressive.
They look even smaller like this.
It feels completely different from the videos we watched.
Now,
I will explain how the Super Kids Dancer Casting Battle works.
Today's Casting Battle...
will be a 1-on-1 battle...
of two dancers.
The first kid dancer to be called will go first.
The next kid dancer to be called will go next.
They will be given 40 seconds to perform.
Once the battle ends,
the directors will go through a thorough discussion...
and must select 1 dancer out of the 2.
When the teams select different dancers,
the selected dancers...
will go to their designated teams.
They will get the team sticker...
from the directors who have chosen them.
However, when the two teams choose the same dancer,
the final decision...
is given to that kid dancer.
(Oh, my gosh!)
If we choose the same dancer,
it's a matter of being chosen or not.
It felt so cruel.
I didn't expect this at all.
It was cruel.
The production crew members felt like perverts.
The dancer will go to the directors of their choice...
to get the team sticker.
The other kid dancer...
will automatically join the other team.
Whenever a 1-on-1 battle ends,
the two teams...
will each cast one dancer.
That team has the advantage.
We're in trouble.
These dancers won't know anything about me.
It's the same with BABYZOO.
They have to decide just by our looks.
Would these kids choose us?
Who are they?
He looks like an actor.
How are we supposed to choose when we don't know them?
"We might not be able to get our targets."
Now this is nice.
There's a certain vibe, you know.
Great energy, great reactions.
I knew the kids would definitely pick up on that.
Wouldn't that make them want to be part of this team even more?
Which Kids Dancers and Directors will end up on the same team?
I can't wait to find out.
Now, let the Super Kids Dancer Casting Battle...
begin!
- Let's go!
(Super Kids Dancer Casting)
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm nervous.
- I just want to dance already.
- Exactly.
The mic...
Aren't we taking the mic off?
They're not going to call me first, are they?
No. I can't do this. No way.
I think they'll stand over there, and we'll stand here...
then face off one pair at a time.
They'll put our photos next to that "VS."
Let's meet the two dancers...
in our first Testing Battle.
- Let's go!
- First, our Super Kids Dancer.
With precise muscle control...
and explosive energy,
she's proven herself worldwide...
Is she a popper?
Jingjing!
(First battler: Jingjing)
Jingjing! Let's go!
You got this!
(First up, Jingjing takes the stage with everyone cheering her on.)
Let's go!
She's getting shy.
She's so good.
What stood out about Jingjing...
(Courtesy of Jingjing)
was that, even at such a young age,
her hits were already pro-level.
She looks so sweet...
but her popping packs a punch. That contrast makes her stand out,
and we needed that on our team.
There's a step later in our routine that's perfect for Jingjing to pop.
When we go, "Bam, bam, bam," some popping would look pretty cool.
- But we do need some popping.
- Yes, we do.
So I wanted Jingjing on our team.
- What about Jingjing?
- For popping?
But we need to see her in action. We really need to see her dance.
Her secondary style is hip-hop.
Then let's go with Nico for now, like we discussed earlier.
I thought featuring her in a scene in this chapter...
would let us showcase more variety,
but the other two felt differently.
I can't wait to see them dance.
The dancer facing Jingjing next...
is confident he'll make his mark with his popping.
That's me.
- Hyo Bin?
- It's Hyo Bin.
Kim Hyo Bin!
(Second battler: Kim Hyo Bin)
Let's go!
(Let's do this!)
(Kim Hyo Bin, 12, South Korea, primary style: popping)
- These kids are pros.
Jingjing's expression just changed.
They're both poppers.
- Too bad. I'd love to have both.
- I know.
Honestly, the style I prefer...
is Hyo Bin's.
He has a really distinct style.
He throws in every skill he's got.
Hyo Bin really understands popping and has incredible technical skills.
(Popping's rising star on Korea's street dance competition circuit)
Another rising star has emerged on Korea's popping scene.
It's a popping showdown.
They're both so talented.
Let's see what level they're on.
I'll be watching for two key things.
First, do they fit our story?
Second, do they fit my story?
We may be competing as teams,
but it's an individual contest, too.
All right, Back Koo Young.
You need to recruit one of these two dancers.
What's your pitch?
Our team has snacks and juice available at all times.
Could you translate that?
We always have snacks and...
(All ears)
It's hot out. You like red bean shaved ice, right?
(A little embarrassed)
That's all I've got.
- Red bean shaved ice?
- Shaved ice.
We can't have any.
Right.
We don't even like shaved ice.
What do we have to offer?
We have pretty ladies.
You have 30 seconds to warm up.
It's a popping showdown.
- Let's go, Jingjing! Come on!
- You got this!
(Cheers louder than at a showdown between national teams)
You got this!
She's stretching right now.
Look. Look.
Just going by their faces, who has more character?
- Jingjing.
- Yes.
But you never know.
Hyo Bin could blow us away.
So if we pick the same dancer,
the kids get to choose their team.
- Right.
- And then...
I think we'll want a lot of the same dancers.
This casting will be a bloodbath.
Jingjing versus Kim Hyo Bin.
Let the battle begin!
- I'm losing my mind!
Ready,
Fight!
- Let's go!
(First dancer: Jingjing)
Her expression changed instantly, just like you said.
(Catch this kiss!)
I thought I was going to faint.
(I'm losing my mind!)
She's got showmanship, too.
Oh, gosh!
She's so good.
She's a master at this.
She even catches every little sound.
That's insane. Oh, gosh!
I want her on our team.
She's good.
(Nonstop praise)
Her execution was truly pro-level.
Her musicality was excellent, too.
She's so, so good.
We really need her on our team.
I'm in love.
She's exactly what our film needs.
She's so expressive.
She's a great dancer.
She's good at more than just popping.
Her overall dance skills were on another level.
(An instant transformation)
(Hearts skip a beat.)
Her vibe is insane.
She struck me as a stylish popper.
Three, two, one. Okay, Kim Hyo Bin!
Jingjing uses her expressions so well.
I love it.
Let's go!
I'll show them what I've prepared.
(Full of anticipation)
(A dopamine rush)
Unbelievable!
Incredible!
(A popping party)
He captures those textures so well.
He's so young, but he really plays with the music.
Oh, gosh!
He was playful,
so witty and full of charisma.
His freestyle skills really blew me away.
He's just having fun out there.
He's totally in the zone.
His charisma is insane.
(Nonstop dopamine rushes)
He's no joke.
(Lost in the moment)
I'm losing my mind!
Five, four,
three, two, one!
(A final dopamine rush)
Battle over!
He absolutely crushed it.
It's okay!
I'm losing my mind.
They're all such natural performers. What do we do?
So cute!
(They end the battle with a friendly exchange.)
But Hyo Bin has great facial expressions, too.
They come out when he dances. He's really good.
Hyo Bin's talent is insane,
but Jingjing's execution is clearly on another level.
We have to choose one.
Each team picks one dancer.
We're in trouble. The first two are already so good.
They're both good. Either way, they're both good.
Jingjing's good, and so is Hyo Bin.
Just whoever fits our film better...
Hyo Bin was better in the battle.
Hyo Bin had the higher highs.
Can Jingjing really match Hyo Bin's talent?
It's about how we'd use a popper.
But if we go with a popper...
I have a spot to showcase them in Chapter Two of my piece.
But I think this dancer could fit...
even without doing any popping.
Let's reveal the casting results.
Will the two teams pick the same dancer or different ones?
- I hope our picks are different.
- I know.
I was a little worried.
If we picked the same dancer, we'd be the ones getting picked.
I hoped our picks would overlap as little as possible.
Your casting boards...
please reveal them!
(3-person team and 4-person team both chose Jingjing.)
Of course, we picked the same one.
Our team chose Jingjing.
This wasn't about who won or lost the battle.
For Chapter One, "Fear,"
our top priority was finding the right dancer for the role.
Should we think about that?
Casting Jingjing as Fear?
There's so much more to Jingjing than meets the eye.
She has such a baby face...
but once she starts popping...
That contrast is really striking.
Fear gaining superpowers...
is a transformation she could really bring to life.
Let's go with Jingjing.
Hyo Bin has no secondary style.
He's all about popping.
Jingjing has a secondary style.
She's so expressive.
She's good at more than just popping.
I wanted someone who could really nail the choreography.
Both teams chose Jingjing.
Now Jingjing gets...
to choose her team.
Now the kid dancer...
gets the final say.
Which team will Jingjing choose?
I had no idea what she'd choose.
I hoped she'd join our team.
We really need her on our team.
Please pick our team.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- So cute.
Yes!
- You were amazing.
- Jingjing has chosen...
the four-person team.
Great job!
- Hyo Bin.
- We'll make you shine, Hyo Bin.
- Thank you!
- Well done.
Why did you choose the four-person team?
Because I think...
the choreographers on this team are really cool.
I've watched their videos for a long time.
A lot really depends on these kids.
Since Hyo Bin joined our team,
I see him differently.
He feels like my own kid now.
They're all good.
Let's make the most of whatever comes our way.
Now, up next...
a head-to-head breaking battle...
(The breaking announcement gets everyone buzzing.)
is about to begin.
Let's go!
- Breaking.
- Please, I don't want to battle.
- Breaking!
Breaking!
Get ready to take your wrist guard off.
Oh, gosh! Oh, gosh!
First up is a dancer...
whose high-difficulty moves...
instantly fire up any battle.
A tiny but powerful b-boy...
- Niuniu.
Niuniu!
(First battler: Niuniu)
(My turn! Peace!)
(An entrance full of star power)
Niuniu!
He even prepared an entrance pose.
He's so tiny.
- Do I take this off?
- Take it off and give it to him.
(Cracking up)
He has to take his mic off to do his breaking moves.
I'm going to give you the sign. Wait for me.
- So cute.
- He's so cute and tiny.
Our little Cocomong.
He was so cute...
I thought it was an ad encouraging us to get married.
But when I saw his videos...
he was pulling off every trick under the sun.
He has that little-kid look we had in mind...
but he can pull off advanced moves.
His dancing is just unreal.
He's such an adorable little guy,
so the contrast is huge.
He's got that little rascal vibe...
If we really play up that side...
Niuniu would make a great character for our film.
Facing him and going second...
with crushing power and explosive impact...
- Sounds like Third Bro to me.
- Power moves...
A b-boy who nails advanced power moves right on the beat.
Third Bro!
(Second battler: Third Bro)
Incredible!
That's insane! That's insane!
- Brothers?
- Aren't they brothers?
Even their haircuts match.
Even the shaved lines mirror each other.
I think they're in the same crew.
(Members of the same Chinese breaking crew)
(Niuniu and Third Bro, friends and rivals in dance battles)
These two are really facing off.
We already had Third Bro on our shortlist.
We should add Third Bro. He's a b-boy.
- He's the best.
- If we get him...
he'd work well in your section.
If we use his tricks to transition between themes...
there's so much we could do.
I know I can count on him.
When it comes to airtime and the scale of moves,
Third Bro definitely has the edge.
But Niuniu holds his own, too.
When you see them side by side,
Niuniu is just so adorable.
So cute.
He's the size of the mic.
Niuniu, you're first.
Please introduce yourself.
He's so precious.
My name is Niuniu.
Nine years old.
(Squealing)
(Overwhelmed by cuteness)
I am Third Bro.
Eleven years old.
That stare!
He's in battle mode.
Third Bro is going to crush it.
- He's going to crush it.
- Yes.
You have 30 seconds to warm up.
(After taking off his mic, )
(Niuniu can finally warm up freely.)
I'm seriously losing my mind.
Third Bro is totally locked in.
That's incredible!
They're both true battlers.
Third Bro is a bit bigger and more intense,
but for the character, I'd pick Niuniu.
But let's choose whoever fits our story better.
Incredible! The sparks are flying.
He's so cool.
You got this! You got this!
Niuniu versus Third Bro.
- Let the battle begin!
- Let's go!
Ready, fight!
I'm confident...
so I don't care who I face.
B-boy Niuniu!
Let's go!
Show us!
Look at that bounce!
This kid is insane!
How is he so light on his feet?
He's practically flying.
(Then I'll do it, too.)
That's unbelievable!
The stage is his playground. He looks so natural out there.
(Poke!)
(Ah!)
(Cheering wildly)
Oh, my gosh!
That's insane!
(Gosh!)
I was in awe.
He executed those moves flawlessly.
I realized he's no ordinary kid.
He went from airflares straight into windmills...
then linked right into headspins.
(Goodness!)
(Niuniu vs. Third Bro)
He even brings out the different instrumental parts.
I wish he were my son.
I really wanted him on our team.
He was so charming.
He's so cute, but his skills are unbelievable.
- That's insane!
- What was that?
Niuniu's such an adorable character.
He's a master b-boy disguised as a little kid.
Oh, gosh!
(That's what I'm talking about!)
I've got chills!
Five, four, three, two, one!
(Wiggling his butt)
(The countdown ends for the first battler, Niuniu.)
(Final pose)
(Copying him)
That gave me serious chills.
Third Bro!
(Second dancer: Third Bro)
I think I can win.
Okay!
- Here he goes.
- Here he goes! Here he goes!
His power and speed are just insane.
The level of technique he showed was just unbelievable.
(Incredible!)
Oh, my gosh!
How is this kid even real?
The level is ridiculously high.
He's just on another level.
He's throwing in every skill...
and every move he can do.
(Bring it on!)
Let's go, Third Bro!
Go!
His execution is way beyond what you'd expect from a kid.
He's flashing smiles and turning on the charm.
(Stunned)
(You talk too much.)
(Calm down.)
There's no substitute for Third Bro's technique.
Does gravity just not apply to him?
Okay!
He's got a chest of steel.
Oh!
Three, two, one!
Battle over!
(See that?)
Hey, sit down. Sit down.
(The MC is flustered.)
It's getting intense in here.
It's getting heated. Really heated.
Peace! That was incredible.
- China's breaking scene is strong.
- Right.
They're going to compete on the world stage.
I think the directors will pick... Niuniu.
Niuniu's specialty is being cute.
They're smitten over there.
Third Bro was so good. So cool.
I think it'll be an even split between these two.
For character, it's Niuniu.
For technique...
For technique, it's Third Bro.
Third Bro definitely excels at power moves.
I can use freestyle in Chapter Three...
I'd go with Niuniu, too.
Niuniu would be better for solo shots showing his character.
Right.
- Let's make our choice now.
- Yes.
- Who do you prefer?
- I think we could really...
fine-tune this kid's performance.
Even if he only gets airborne once,
he can still come in strong in that section.
But look. Think about it.
Two people are standing here.
They split off to either side.
Should Niuniu come out then, or should Third Bro?
In that case, I'd go with Niuniu.
Because there's plenty of character.
This kind of dancer...
We already have that covered with this kid here.
I can picture some things with Niuniu in Chapter Two...
But I'd go with Third Bro, then.
I really wanted him for my part, so I made my case.
I'd go with Third Bro. We're split.
If we think about the judging, Third Bro would be better...
I actually think the opposite.
Really?
They must still be figuring out their concept...
I don't know.
Maybe it doesn't work for BADA. It must not be a good fit for her.
Are you going to use Third Bro?
Third Bro? That's the plan.
- You're going to use him?
- Yes, I am.
I absolutely need Niuniu for the chapter I have in mind.
But...
Four,
- I'll go along with you.
- three, two,
(Finally agreeing to go with the team's choice)
one.
- What do you think? Not him?
- I don't think so.
You don't think so?
They're split. Totally split.
Your casting board...
I really wanted him on our team this time.
I think I was pretty nervous.
Please reveal them!
(Niuniu vs. Third Bro)
They chose different dancers.
(3-person team: Niuniu 4-person team: Third Bro)
A peace treaty!
See? We think alike.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for dancing.
Great job!
You did a good job!
- Nice, nice.
- That was awesome.
- Let's go!
- Third Bro, seriously...
- I love you!
- The final casting results.
So cute.
- That was the hardest one yet.
- It was so hard.
- It's a bit of a shame.
- Yes.
It's a bit of a shame.
He's so cute, I can't take it. I'm losing my mind.
I realized with Niuniu that I can't let them slip away.
I think I need to fight harder for the dancers I want.
Now, let's meet the two dancers...
in our next Testing Battle.
- Let's go!
- Our first battler...
From China to Tokyo and Paris,
a hip-hop powerhouse who's conquered the world stage...
Stand up right away.
Song Haoming!
(See? I told you!)
(Super Kids Dancer Casting: Song Haoming)
(Song Haoming, 13, China, primary style: hip-hop)
Those high-waisted pants make him look like a total pro.
He already looked extraordinary.
Tucked-in pants and a Red Bull hat.
He's got to be a good dancer.
I was looking forward to Song Haoming.
Among the kid dancers nowadays,
it's no exaggeration to say that he's the top.
(The global winner...)
(of the 2025 WDC Tokyo Finals, Kids Division)
(The global winner of the 2026 RF Jam Junior Open Styles)
Very aggressive and has no hesitation.
He can use his body freely to dance.
He was on my wish list of dancers.
Song Haoming?
Haoming has good techniques.
- He'll do very well with freestyle.
- Yes.
- Song Haoming?
- Song Haoming.
Does Haoming do breaking too?
Hip hop and popping. But he does do breaking techniques.
He does choreography too.
- Shall we get Haoming?
- Yes.
Song Haoming has a lot of skills,
- so he's a good candidate.
- Agreed.
The dancer he will face...
has won multiple kids dance battles.
- Let's go.
- With confident energy, Jack.B.
Jack.B.
(Cheering)
- Go!
- This is going to be fun.
Yes.
(Go, Jack. B!)
The directors really like Jack.B.
Actually, Jack. B was in the top three...
of our list.
Whether it's the turn or the conclusion,
he can really lead the story as the main character.
For our film, especially for Chapter Four,
we needed someone who gave off positive and happy vibe...
with his face.
He has star quality,
his expressions are naughty and cheeky,
and he acts well according to the concept.
He exudes the happy energy.
We must bring Jack.B.
What do you think about Jack. B?
He's very expressive.
That's right. First of all, we can have smooth communication,
and he's a good dancer.
I don't think they were into it.
(Watching Jack. B's video)
He is good, but I thought...
his character was rather conventional.
I'll see how he does during the casting.
- Let's go, Jack.B.
- Go, Song Haoming.
Let's go.
- Yes, stretch.
- Jack.B.
He gives off a happy vibe.
- He has a positive vibe.
- Yes.
Haoming...
has the good-dancer face too.
- He's very good.
- Like a mischievous baby.
Will the quality or the character win?
Song Haoming versus Jack.B.
The dancers' battle starts.
Ready? Fight!
Let's go!
Kill the beat and go lightly.
The momentary control of strength.
Nice energy. That's so powerful.
Oh, my gosh.
What's that?
He's not just a kid. He's a master.
He was so well-balanced.
He plays with the rhythm.
- This is crazy.
- Amazing.
All his movements are tightly choreographed.
I lost my mind when I watched him dance.
His dance quality was impressive.
He really is a hip hop battler.
What's with Song Haoming?
He's so good.
He looks at his opponent and dances as if he's showing off.
(Amazing)
He danced freestyle hip hop...
like he was a martial arts expert.
(I lost.)
I was tempted.
He'd do well with me.
Three, two, one, switch.
That was so good.
(The second dancer, Jack. B)
- Let's go, Jack. B!
- Let's go!
I really want him on my crew.
You're on fire!
He's very stable.
He shows the impact clearly.
He sure has star quality.
His face already shows the character.
He's so relaxed.
He leads the dance with so much energy.
Thinking on his feet and killing the beat like that.
The humor and the strength control.
- He makes great use of his face.
- That's it.
Jack. B is so good.
He's so good.
(Amazing)
Jack. B was so much better in real life than in the video.
We must get Jack. B on our team no matter what.
- Five, four, three, - Gosh, look at Jack.B.
two, one. Battle...
over.
He knows what a show is.
(They end the casting battle with a happy high five.)
They're really good.
You two are so cool.
I feel dizzy.
This is insane.
Let's discuss.
He really is good at acting.
He'll be captured nicely in a film.
And if we don't get who we want...
for the protagonist,
he could become...
- the third candidate for it.
- I thought that too.
Yes, he can do that.
We wanted those with good expressions,
so Jack. B was very appealing to us.
I thought he had star quality...
and would take in all the directions we gave him.
I think they want him too.
Sim Hee Jung.
Don't try to look at what I'm ticking.
I'm not looking.
(I'm watching you.)
- They definitely want Jack.B.
- I think so too.
We need to appeal this.
That we have a character we want to give him.
- We must appeal this to him.
- We must tell him.
The kids thought they gained courage...
through the masks,
but the courage was within themselves.
That's the message of the film we're making.
Let the kids wear masks.
They dance really well with the masks on.
(Like this.)
(Laughing)
(Discussing the mask design with the styling team)
Jack. B would look good in a rabbit mask,
and he'd suit our concept well.
This rabbit mask belongs to Jack.B.
Please reveal the casting board!
Here it comes.
(Both teams chose Jack.B.)
As I thought, we chose the same dancer.
He has star quality, is a great dancer,
and has great stage presence too.
There's no reason not to pick him.
It means their team needs Jack. B for their story.
"Do they have a similar plot as ours?"
Which team...
will Jack. B choose?
Let's find out his choice.
Here he goes.
(Jack. B starts walking)
Please come to us.
I hope Jack. B will come to us.
(Jack. B chooses the 4-person team.)
Welcome.
Very nice.
I told you we were on a roll.
Things are going as per our strategy.
I was relieved.
We got one main character at least.
Thank you.
- You were amazing.
- Let's do it.
Thank you.
For Song Haoming,
we wanted him initially too.
So we'll do well with him.
The next two kids for the casting battle...
have danced together as partners for a long time.
And are also rivals who've gone on the same stages...
countless times and have grown together.
Are they A Zheng and Axun?
It must be those two.
Then it really might be us.
The first dancer is Xunxun.
- Let's go.
Okay.
The most dancers of my chapter...
are Xunxun, A Zheng...
The dancers I want to pick first are A Zheng and Xunxun.
The second dancer to go against him...
- A Zheng.
- is A Zheng.
(A Zheng, 14, male, Main genre: Popping, old school)
(Super Kids Dancer Casting Battle)
I knew those two would fight.
Everyone has been waiting for this.
The big match between Xunxun and A Zheng.
The only two dancers who can pull off difficult choreo...
are Xunxun and A Zheng.
They'll be given important roles.
They're from the same place.
(They've danced together for a long time...)
(in the same dance school.)
- They're dressed the same too.
- You're right.
I thought they won't let us take both of them.
If at least one of them came to our team,
they'd play a very big role.
So we wrote A Zheng and Xunxun...
as the 1st and 2nd dancers we want.
There's high chance...
- we'll only get 1 out of the 2.
- Definitely.
They showed perfect chemistry together.
But today, they're battling each other...
to win the directors' choices.
I know these guys.
They're good.
(Rooting for each other as a rival and a brother...)
(before the battle starts)
We might change our minds after watching the battle too.
Xunxun versus A Zheng.
The dancers' battle starts now.
Ready? Fight!
(Xunxun goes first.)
Let's go.
They're really like twins.
The way he feels the rhythm is different.
In a battle, it's important to set the mood.
He popped really well.
He's skilled. He's good.
He's so good.
I was shocked.
He was even better in real life.
He's good at rocking too.
He's a good dancer.
He was so good that I was surprised.
He has long arms and legs,
so his moves are big and clear.
What's this?
He suddenly started popping.
I want him.
He's so good.
The quality of his popping is really good.
He dances all genres.
He's an all-rounder.
He can dance many genres.
He's so good.
His age shows.
He's so powerful.
Xunxun's moves are more skilled and seasoned.
Five, four,
three, two, one. Switch.
(Surprised)
How did he stand up?
My gosh!
Xunxun is good.
My top choice is A Zheng.
A Zheng, you need to take the stage. You can do it.
He has his style. He's cool.
Let's go.
He uses the rocking combination and gives a variation.
Crazy legs.
A Zheng has a bigger range.
His moves are big,
which satisfies you visually.
A Zheng has star quality.
A Zheng is really cool.
He is no joke too.
His moves are angled very accurately.
(He's so good.)
He's wilder.
As a solo dancer, A Zheng will stand out more.
He's good.
He knows how to look cool.
He's witty.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Battle over.
(Xunxun and A Zheng's casting battle is over.)
They're so good.
They're not just good at choreography.
- They just...
- They're good at all genres.
They're all-rounders.
That was impressive.
They live up to their names.
Both of them are so good.
It'll take a long time to discuss.
I think they could change their decision too.
A Zheng suits the kid concept more,
- but Xunxun is a better dancer.
- Definitely.
But A Zheng is expressive.
We have many expressive dancers already.
It's good if all of them are.
If he's at the center,
isn't it a bit weak?
I don't think he'll look weak in a video.
- That's true.
- Since it's not a stage.
He's really on the ball.
If we cast A Zheng,
- we need to draw it out of him.
- Yes.
That will become our role.
Both of them...
will be drawn out if we direct them.
Let's check the casting results.
Did they choose the same or different dancers?
We must've chosen the same.
Even if we overlap?
(We can't overlap.)
Please reveal the casting board.
(3-person team chose A Zheng, and 4-person team chose Xunxun.)
(We chose different dancers!)
(Relieved)
- This is how we're split.
- They've chosen different dancers.
A Zheng feels...
more raw,
less organized.
We thought...
it'd look nice in the film.
I really found that vibe of his charming.
Thinking about the film, we should choose Xunxun.
What we wanted to portray...
with Xunxun and A Zheng...
were the bold characters.
It can give off the "I'll scold you as the older one" vibe.
(If we cast Xunxun)
That would look nice too.
Jingjing will do popping at first,
and Xunxun will appear as a role...
which protects Jingjing. After looking at her like this,
if he does something right away,
that in itself could become the wow point.
So we chose Xunxun.
We were confident.
(Xunxun is cast in the 4-person team.)
Nice.
(A Zheng is cast in the 3-person team.)
When I see him up close,
he has a even better image.
Yes.
We should remove his cap first thing.
In a nutshell, we cast the dancer...
who was our topmost priority.
Our film will be very interesting story-wise.
It's interesting now.
Let's meet the next dancers of the casting battle.
Who will it be?
Hurry up and show us the next battle!
The first dancer to go...
dances dynamic hip hop...
to fancy tricking.
He has explosive energy.
Hinowa.
(Hinowa, 12, male, Main genre: Hip hop, from Japan)
(The first dancer is Hinowa.)
(Looking forward to him)
Let's go!
Look at him.
This is crazy.
He's playful.
Hinowa's dancing has very good quality,
and his character is clear.
He has solid foundation...
of hip hop and the steps.
The dancer to go against him...
is an expert at expressing the vibe and the nuance of hip hop.
It's Rittagun.
Let's go!
(The second dancer is Rittagun.)
Rittagun...
has a huge range of his bounce,
so those who watch him dance feel very satisfied.
I was looking forward to Rittagun.
I love their characters.
This is crazy.
They're having a civil war.
It's hard to watch...
because I wanted to have both Rittagun and Hinowa on my team.
Anyone you want?
The two Japanese hip hop dancers.
(Preferred dancers of Chapter 3: Hinowa and Rittagun)
When it comes to old school hip hop,
it's hard to find that kind of vibe from kids nowadays.
Their movements transcend generations.
Picking 1 out of the 2...
is very difficult.
I'm Sawamoto Hinowa.
Nice to meet you.
I may be on the same team as him,
but I want to win.
I'm Ritta. Nice to meet you.
I'll rip him apart with all I have.
(Surprised)
I really like this. I love it.
- That's scary.
- Interesting.
- Ritta is cool.
- He's cool.
That's intense.
Hinowa and Rittagun.
The two dancers' battle starts now.
The rascals' battle.
They're both going to do hip hop. No doubt.
I'm sure they'll do Japanese-style hip hop which uses big movements.
- Ready?
- Let's go!
Fight!
Let's go!
(Hinowa goes first.)
The moment I saw his moves,
I thought it was cool.
Rocking?
His main genre is hip hop, but he does rocking.
He can dance different genres.
Yes, nice.
That's good energy.
(Thrilling)
He's no joke.
Rocking.
Here goes the ham.
He had various expressions.
He was showing off himself,
and it caught my eye.
Hinowa is good.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Switch!
(The next dancer is Rittagun.)
He's telling you to stand up.
(Looking forward to it)
(Taunting)
(Dopamine explodes)
He's flying.
He's so powerful.
He's so aggressive and good.
He's such a good dancer.
I was so surprised.
He's so cool.
How can he make those moves...
at his age?
How can that young guy have such style...
and attitude?
He's the embodiment of hip hop.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Battle over.
(Hinowa and Rittagun's casting battle is over.)
(Amazed)
- They're amazing.
- That was great.
(Tension up)
But Hinowa...
did rocking when his main genre was hip hop.
- What do you think?
- But...
he didn't get a hip hop song.
I want to see him dance hip hop.
This might be too sudden,
but to see how well they work together,
why don't we have a simultaneous battle?
(Agreeing wholeheartedly)
Let's go.
Ready? Fight!
They'll show us Japanese-style hip hop.
(Hinowa and Rittagun's simultaneous battle starts.)
I'm having high expectations.
I liked how it was cute and cool.
- They're cool.
Let's go.
(Amazing chemistry)
(They're perfect together.)
I was impressed by their energy.
It was explosive.
It's Japanese-style old school hip hop.
They're both so good.
What?
Hinowa...
was enjoying the stage.
Rittagun was so cool.
His presence itself was cool.
(Hinowa versus Rittagun)
Oh, my gosh.
Let's go!
Okay, all set.
(The feeling lingers.)
(BADA is amazed.)
I really wanted them both.
I can't choose one.
Discuss thoroughly...
and choose a kid dancer...
you want to cast.
What should we do?
I think...
they're both of the same level that it doesn't really matter.
Thinking about our choreography though,
since Hinowa knows rocking,
wouldn't he learn faster when we teach him?
- I think so. Then we go with him?
- Me too.
(The 3-person team has decided.)
I think they will...
choose him too.
Then...
it'll be a repeat...
of what happened.
Let's check the casting results.
Please reveal them!
- I think we chose differently.
- I think we chose the same.
Did they choose the same or different dancers?
(Hinowa)
(Both 3-person team and 4-person team chose Hinowa.)
(We chose the same dancer again?)
We think alike.
Our choices keep overlapping.
Judging from how our choices keep overlapping,
our climaxes must have similar vibes.
What we need to express.
The final decision...
is in the kid dancer's hands.
For our film, the bright side was the most important.
We wanted more dancers who could give off happy vibes.
I thought we must have him on our team.
He's very smart at expressing the song,
and he has a definitive character.
He's crucial...
to our film.
We need him at all costs.
(Thinking hard)
He's thinking really hard.
(Which team will Hinowa choose?)
Which team?
Please.
I hope he'll join our team.
(Hinowa chooses the 4-person team.)
Welcome.
Ritta, come on!
(Rittagun joins the 3-person team.)
Actually, image-wise, we wanted Rittagun.
We just chose Hinowa because he seemed to be...
the more obedient type.
But we make good use of...
those who join our team.
That was when I started to feel ominous.
If this continues,
whenever our choices overlap with theirs,
there would be no way we could ever take him.
I should've been grinding hard on social media.
- We need to make a killer piece.
- Right.
Let's just make the best out of whatever we have.
(Celebrating)
Hinowa.
Thanks!
Nice!
(My friend just took 1st place!)
He's so cool.
- How could he be so cool?
- I told you he was cool.
He even showed respect.
That just gave me goosebumps.
His attitude.
We should stop roasting each other then.
Show some respect, will you?
I'll introduce the next two dancers stepping up for the casting battle.
Rich grooves and explosive energy.
A hip-hop performer who shines even brighter on stage.
Honatsu.
(First Battler: Honatsu)
(Honatsu, 14 years old, female, hip-hop, Japan)
- Finally!
- Let's go!
Honatsu is amazing.
Honatsu reminds me of Kyoka.
Should I call her the textbook of Japanese hip-hop?
No matter what movement she executes,
it looks so effortlessly seasoned.
It feels like her stylistic range...
is just broad and limitless.
She has a level of execution you don't see at her age.
Her dance caliber is unreal.
I could feel the master's aura on her.
The dancer, stepping up to battle second.
Authentic Afro vibes mastered straight...
- from the motherland in Africa.
- It's her.
An Afro dancer owning the stage with unparalleled groove.
ShiN!
(ShiN, 13 years old, female, Afro, Japan)
(A big fan of ShiN is here.)
- Let's go!
She's amazing.
She's really good.
This is just...
ShiN's dancing itself just feels on another level.
House, hip-hop, Afro...
It felt like there was nothing she couldn't pull off.
I've never seen an Asian dancer pull off Amapiano to that level.
The Afro feel...
cutting through the footwork and syncopated rhythms...
is authentic African steps and vibes.
On our preliminary casting wishlist,
they were the ones we had ranked 1st and 2nd.
I want to take 1 of these 2.
Is this number one?
Watching the film, your heart will lean completely toward ShiN.
- Right.
- I agree.
Look, if we can't get ShiN, who will you pick?
If we don't get ShiN...
- We have to take Honatsu.
- Honatsu.
We want to recruit them both,
We would keep Honatsu as our second pick...
assuming we could recruit both,
but they're facing each other?
I'm Honatsu. Nice to meet you.
(Expectant)
I will tear up the floor.
(She's so cool!)
First, I'm just going to have fun.
I will do my best to dance...
in my own style.
Thank you.
(Both of you, good luck!)
They both look so cool.
Just watching this battle is insane.
This battle is crazy.
This is going to be a great match.
The battle between the two dancers begins now.
I can't wait.
Your eyes are sparkling...
for the very first time on this show.
My eyes are sparkling.
I'm having so much fun.
- I have to watch closely.
- Let's go!
Show them what you've got.
Ready?
Fight!
(First Battler: Honatsu)
Look at that composure.
Look at the seamless flow.
This is insane.
Honatsu is just incredible.
She's just amazing.
How is her body this flexible?
She is so captivating.
(She's so talented.)
A true master's aura.
- It's insane.
- Her technique and footwork...
are impossibly seasoned for someone so young.
She synchronized with the music.
If you turned Yoon Mi Rae's rap into dance,
this is what it would look like.
- Look at the last move. It's crazy.
- Three, two,
one. Switch! ShiN!
(Second Battler: ShiN)
I got goosebumps.
(ShiN is warming up.)
(Shocked)
What do I do with her?
Look at her face.
(Impressed)
(This is beautiful.)
ShiN was possessed.
She's the best here.
She's the all-mighty dancer.
(This is exciting.)
(Unbelievable)
I fell in love.
That was crazy.
For a moment, I was synchronized with her.
She is insane.
Her talent, individuality, and style were already fully formed.
(Dropping to the knees)
(She's the best.)
Three, two, one.
The battle is over.
That was crazy.
A hit straight to my heart.
This was the most thrilling moment of 2026.
That was completely unreal.
Nothing else matters anymore.
This is insane.
(Shocked)
Both of them were really...
Her performance was incredible.
That was great.
- I got goosebumps.
- It was insane.
Look at this.
It was like a master versus a master.
They are insanely good.
They are unbelievable.
They're just too good.
She can do it all.
I know. She can pull off anything.
Her facial expressions are amazing too.
I just fell in love.
Okay. I already know your pick without even hearing it.
I'm in love.
Let's check the casting results.
Please reveal...
(Which dancer did the two teams choose?)
the casting board.
(Both the 3-person team and the 4-person team chose ShiN.)
They both want her.
We're in trouble.
Our picks clashed again.
The final decision rests with ShiN.
Please give me a second.
All four of us want you so desperately.
- We want to create...
- Open your arms wide.
a phenomenal spotlight for ShiN in a crucial part.
We're sure about that.
They're ready to welcome her.
I wished so desperately for us to get chosen.
Listen.
Tell her that we built ours with ShiN in mind,
and she will be center stage for more than half of it.
Being on this show keeps making me desperate.
I mean, so little has gone...
according to our plans so far.
She was the ideal candidate for our main character.
To be honest,
the three of us built...
the entire routine...
from the start...
with ShiN as our lead.
It was the exact same for us.
- That's a lie.
- It's definitely not a lie.
It's a lie.
The recruiting war for top talent has begun.
Honestly, we'd be so happy even if Honatsu joins us.
That's true.
We're happy with Honatsu as well.
- Letting her go is just tough.
- It's a shame to lose her.
It's such a shame. That's what makes it so hard.
Wait. Please give me a minute.
This must be such a tough decision to make.
Come to our team.
Join our team.
You guys should back off.
(Look over here.)
Why do I have a feeling she will pick the other team?
- I know.
- No.
Fight.
(ShiN is standing at the crossroads of choice.)
Please, ShiN!
- ShiN!
I really hope she picks us.
I hope she can feel our sincerity.
(What is ShiN's final choice?)
(ShiN selects the 4-person team.)
(Those who won ShiN)
(Those who lost ShiN)
We lost one again.
The kids will always pick the other team.
Because they have BADA. It can't be helped.
When it comes to popularity, BADA is number one here.
I want to ask as well.
Why did they choose our team?
Was there no one in your team who could match her?
Come on. No one can beat her.
No one.
(Honatsu joins the 3-person team.)
- Welcome aboard, Honatsu.
- Welcome.
Honatsu is a great dancer too.
All we have to do is direct a performance...
tailored to her strengths and capture it on camera,
so it is fine.
What worries me is that...
we now have to get the next lead.
Is there anyone who could even qualify...
as a main character candidate?
No, right?
I say Rittagun.
Rittagun?
He has a distinct character. But...
But he's more like the genius archetype.
(The 3-person team's main character is still yet to be found.)
Who that main character will be remains undecided.
That's the part that worries me.
(In the 1st 2 casting battles, they picked 1 dancer each.)
(They successfully recruited the kid dancer they wanted.)
(But the peace was short-lived.)
(The two teams' picks continuously overlapped.)
I was great. I was so thrilled.
Now that they chose us,
I think we have to create an even better film.
I am getting worried.
- We have no real say in this.
- Right.
Whenever our picks overlap, they always go to the other team.
Who will be our main character?
I think we need to pivot to Plan B...
instead of our original Plan A.
We need to recruit better dancers.
I felt anxious and concerned.
We have caught the perfect momentum.
Maybe we can recruit every single kid dancer we want.
The upcoming casting battle is...
Who is up next now? It can't be them next to us, right?
I feel like my turn is coming up soon.
What do I do?
A world-class competition champion...
armed with versatile technique and explosive energy.
A breaking dancer.
- It is B-Boy Qiuqiu.
- It's him.
Qiuqiu!
(Super Kids Dancer Casting Battle)
(Qiuqiu, 14 years old, male, breaking, China)
Let's go!
He's a breaking dancer, right?
Break a leg!
(Suddenly taking his shirt off?)
(Flustered)
(Chuckling)
Look at Lip J
(Qiuqiu approaches Lip J)
(An unexpected challenge)
Look at those six-pack abs.
Those abs are insane. You look so cool.
I'm not taking off the mic?
(Shaking her head)
Okay.
Qiuqiu is world-class.
His career history at that age is unbelievable.
He is a pure battler, and he has the physique of a pro.
He delivers remarkably seasoned breaking.
I think he can deliver breaking built for genuine showmanship.
So I had high expectations.
The second battler is a dancer...
armed with powerful hip-hop moves and acrobatics.
- A hip-hop dancer.
- There is barely anyone left.
A dancer defined by speed and overflowing energy.
Yurichika, it's you.
(Suddenly feeling nervous)
Yurichika!
(Qiuqiu versus Yurichika)
Go, Yurichika!
(Yurichika, 13 years old, female, hip-hop, Japan)
I'm so excited.
Yurichika was my number-one pick the very day...
I first received the dancer profiles.
(Back Koo Young is watching Yurichika's clip.)
She's incredible.
Yurichika...
(Amazed)
Looking at her, all you can say is this.
(Impressed)
She's the next Kyoka.
I had only seen her video,
but just from that, I could tell she was a talented dancer.
I thought that if we recruited her, it would be game over.
Her sub-genre is acrobatics, and her main genre is hip-hop?
Acrobatics is her sub-genre?
Then there will be nothing she can't do.
I can't believe they let Yurichika and Qiuqiu battle.
If we fail to cast...
both A Zheng and Xunxun...
and have to pick our main character candidate...
- Yurichika?
- Yes, Yurichika.
That can be an option.
Yurichika already has a storyline written on her face.
I want Qiuqiu.
I think it'd be nice to have a B-boy.
The newly selected backup candidates for the main character...
were Qiuqiu and Yurichika.
Both Qiuqiu and Yurichika...
were dancers I coveted.
Do you have kid dancers you want as top priorities?
Yurichika and Honatsu.
It makes sense that MIN JUN wants her.
I know.
I really wanted to bring Yurichika in.
I wanted to cast her as Fear.
She acts all timid, but the second she dances, she changes...
and her side as a kid completely vanishes.
She was the character archetype I wanted to include.
If we fail to recruit the Third Bro,
there's someone who can fill in for the part.
- Qauqau? Qiuqiu?
- Right.
- Qauqau?
The trajectory of the synergy he can generate is enormous.
So I bet the 3-person team...
is having the same plan to recruit him.
A showdown between a B-boy and a hip-hop dancer.
Please introduce yourself.
I will blow you up.
(Cool!)
Qiuqiu is boiling over.
I just asked him for an introduction,
and he declared war.
Yurichika,
you should make a proper declaration of war too.
(Deep in thought)
(High expectations)
I will tear him up with everything I have.
(She's so cute.)
How adorable.
Dancers, please get ready for the battle.
(Chuckling)
What do I do?
Yurichika is going to show acrobatics, right?
(Taking it off again)
Look at those abs.
He's showing off so hard.
I think he's showing it off on purpose.
Go all out, Qiuqiu.
He's steeling his resolve.
World competition champion.
(The world champion's warm-up to assert dominance)
He's showing it off on purpose.
He won already. Yurichika is totally intimidated.
She's just stretching her legs.
In terms of genre, the two are different,
but we already have Niuniu for breaking.
If we want to showcase heavy breaking,
we'd need Qiuqiu.
Otherwise, I would love to have Yurichika.
I tried to watch closely so we could make the best use...
of their dancing and movement.
The battle between the two dancers begins now.
Ready!
- Fight!
- Let's go!
Let's go, Qiuqiu!
His leg extension range is massive.
My goodness. Just how much did he practice that?
(Qiuqiu versus Yurichika)
Does this even make sense?
Keeping balance with such moves...
is an insane level of difficulty.
And in that position...
When you see something overwhelming, you become speechless.
Goosebumps break out, and every hair stands on end.
It was awe-inspiring.
How is this even possible? Isn't this insane?
My goodness.
(Qiuqiu versus Yurichika)
You're incredible.
(Amazed)
I wanted to recruit Qiuqiu.
This is insane.
- It's impossible.
- This is incredible.
I'm totally hooked. It's legendary.
How can kid B-boys...
execute skills at such an elite level?
He looks like Bruce Lee.
He was defying the laws of physics.
Come on!
I wanted to bring him onto our team so badly.
Two, one.
Switch! Yurichika!
He's not a kid.
He totally nailed it.
Two, one.
(Switch!)
Let's go!
(The second battler: Yurichika)
(Qiuqiu versus Yurichika)
Her sense of rhythm is incredible, as expected.
Her facial expressions were remarkably dynamic.
Let's go!
Look at that move. That's crazy.
I really want Yurichika.
She is definitely going to excel at everything.
She's amazing.
She's insanely good.
Watching a young girl dancer throw down hip-hop moves...
felt really unique.
(The music suddenly cuts off.)
(Yurichika keeps dancing without missing a beat.)
She was caught off guard...
by the edited audio track,
(She was caught off guard.)
but carried on seamlessly without showing it.
It was unbelievable.
She's so talented and seasoned.
Her musicality is incredible, and she is just insanely good.
- Hey!
- There you go!
Three, two, one.
The battle is over!
(The casting battle between Qiuqiu and Yurichika is over.)
That was amazing.
- They're just so good.
- It was unbelievable.
Wasn't Yurichika amazing at the beginning?
She looked so tough.
That was such a high-level battle.
Qiuqiu, you're so cool.
Wouldn't they choose Qiuqiu without question?
When it comes to breaking, Qiuqiu is the best.
- Right. He's the one.
- He's the final boss.
He is the king of B-boys here.
It makes sense why he swept world competitions.
It's unreal.
What do we do?
You want to pick this one?
- We should.
- What about this one?
Strategically speaking, I think we should pick this one.
- Because...
- I agree.
If we have her, we can make her the main character.
We can just use him for the big-impact move.
What if she goes to the other team?
- What if she leaves us?
- That's impossible.
What if she does?
It will never happen.
That scenario doesn't even exist.
- What do you think?
- They'll definitely pick this one.
(Predicting the 4-person team will choose Yurichika)
They immediately pointed to her.
(Kasper was watching everything.)
(Nodding his head)
Should we clash picks and get abandoned again?
Or...
(The men have grown accustomed to being abandoned.)
That's hilarious.
This is crazy.
I am prepared to die as many times as it takes.
- I don't mind it either.
- The thing is,
do we stack spectacle on top of spectacle?
Or do we go with pure choreography?
First off, both are so good.
Qiuqiu is just overwhelmingly good.
We could try some heavy breaking.
Already having secured Niuniu for breaking,
when considering whether we have enough scenes...
to maximize the synergy...
between Qiuqiu and Niuniu...
You know I'm using this element.
If they follow right after the bandage dance...
Doing it solo is quite typical.
We still need a main character.
I was solely fixated on the main character.
Could Qiuqiu actually pull off the main character?
(Who did the two teams choose?)
Please reveal the casting board.
(Both teams chose Yurichika.)
Our choices clashed again, as expected.
We might not...
be able to recruit her.
(It overlapped again.)
I guess they went with a similar strategy to ours.
To me, Qiuqiu was just on a different level.
I completely fell in love with him.
Based purely on the battle, it had to be Qiuqiu.
But the dilemma was that...
we already had a breaking dancer on our team.
I wasn't sure if casting another breaker was the right move.
So we decided to cast a hip-hop dancer...
since we were missing hip-hop as a genre.
So we chose Yurichika.
I'm getting the feeling that...
we could consider him to take the lead role.
- I was pushing for him.
- Yes.
Right. That's what I remember.
You wanted Yurichika.
- She has an androgynous charm.
- Yes.
I mean, she's got that look.
- Isn't she perfect in films?
- Yes, she is.
She's got that look.
I thought we needed a dancer...
with expressive eyes and strong facial expressions.
Considering my approach, I checked all the boxes...
when she was battling...
and dancing.
I had this feeling that she could take the lead role.
(Which team will she pick?)
I really want Yurichika on my team.
Why is she walking toward right like the others?
She would pick us, wouldn't she?
Please.
(Yurichika picks the 3-person team.)
- No way!
- My gosh.
(Shocked)
(I can't believe this!)
(At last!)
(No way!)
She went to the team with Mr. Koo Young, Mr. Kasper,
and Uncle BABYZOO.
I was heartbroken.
- I'm so touched.
- Thank you.
- Yurichika!
I liked BABYZOO, so I chose the three-person team.
Thank you so much for picking us.
To us, Yurichika is like a deity.
When we tried to find the right dancer to take the lead role,
we came up empty.
Then she came to save us.
She really is a lifesaver.
- Qiuqiu.
You're number one.
(Qiuqiu will join the 4-person team.)
Qiuqiu. Let's go.
This is interesting.
- That was crazy.
- What a surprise.
We're good now. We can afford to lose here on out.
(Just happy)
It feels great to be chosen.
I mean it.
I was really surprised.
(It feels this good?)
How do you feel now?
My heart sank for a moment.
Your heart sank, right? Boom.
It's been like that for us the whole time.
Only one casting battle remains now.
It's Rikka versus Sun Manhang.
It was the last battle.
I tried to figure out what to look for in this battle.
Rikka specializes in jazz-focused choreography.
Sun Manhang specializes in hip-hop-focused choreography.
Their main genres are different.
I'm wondering what kind of energy they'll show us.
- Which one should we pick?
- We were trying to figure that out.
We were chosen by the dancers we wanted.
It'd be nice to get a dancer for a position we're missing.
Ready, fight.
Let's go!
- Gosh.
- She was at the top of my list.
Let's go, Rikka!
(Captivated)
I love it.
She's super talented.
Switch.
(Sun Manhang is next.)
He's having fun.
(Nervous)
(Impressed)
- He's good!
- He's great.
- He's good.
- What?
I had no idea he was that good.
He danced perfectly on the beat.
Hey, he's so good.
He was in complete control.
(Bobbing his head)
(That's some crazy confidence.)
Battle over.
I was impressed by his dancing.
Actually, we weren't considering casting...
Sun Manhang at first.
As soon as I saw him dance, he won me over.
We absolutely needed him for our film.
I thought he'd be great for bringing that extra flavor to our film.
(Their decisions overlapped even to the last casting battle.)
This is legendary.
Please join our team.
Which team...
will he choose?
Okay.
(Should I go to them or not?)
Please.
He's playful.
We need him on our team.
(Which team will this playful dancer pick?)
(He picks the 4-person team.)
- Okay. He chose...
- Thank you.
the four-person team.
(Rikka picks the 3-person team.)
Rikka is great too.
I'm sure she'll shine more on our team.
It's a pity, but what could I do?
We haven't tried anything with them yet.
We must make it work no matter what.
I'll do my best.
"Super Kids Direct Mission, Judges' Evaluation."
"Stay in your Directors' Room."
(What's going on?)
(They're bringing in chairs?)
My gosh. Come on. This is crazy.
I'm going to watch the judges watch it?
(With the glass wall between us?)
(Right before my eyes?)
(Screaming)
(Knocked out)
(The judges start evaluating with everyone watching.)
(It worked!)
(Wild applause from the judges)
(We got it. That's the reaction.)
(Nice!)
(So cute!)
Four of the seven directors...
will head to Last Stage: 24H.
Four of the seven directors?
(This is super cool.)
(Who's that?)
(Revealing the kids' film that drove the judges mad)
Is that you?
(15 days left until the shoot of the film)
(The day of the production meeting)
The film director is here.
We'll start the meeting now.
Sung Jin has a lot of experience with filming dance videos.
(Jennie's performance video)
He also worked a lot with INGYOO and Simeez.
I've worked with him once before.
I'm in charge of Chapter One.
The intro will be included in Chapter One.
She's going to school like any other day.
Then she finds a door that leads to a different world.
- Four or five dancers?
- So she can't be confident?
- Exactly. A group of timid kids.
- Right. They'd be like this.
"I want to be like them." That's the idea.
Timid dancers...
find masks.
- When they put the masks on...
- It happens here.
Oh, my. They turn into Super Kids.
It's like they're under a spell. "Hey, you try it on too."
The plot will heighten in my chapter.
There will be a battle in my chapter.
This is the most powerful part of the film.
Then the mask comes off and gets destroyed.
When it comes off, it'd be like... "I'm doomed."
"What if I can't dance?"
The masks didn't make them good dancers. The truth is,
the masks gave them courage.
After building up the plot, there will be a dance break.
- Everyone will dance together.
- Yes.
I'm in charge of Chapter Four.
When they're all running out, we're going to bring in the rain.
The energy level will build up throughout the film.
Then it will just blow up with the rain.
They're going to dance in the rain. After that...
The audience sees that...
we were the ones who put the masks there.
We're going to place the masks somewhere else again.
- For the next generation.
- Yes.
It might come across as light.
But kids should keep things light, not heavy.
We can't make this difficult.
(On the same day, the 3-person team has a production meeting too.)
(Director Back Koo Young is abroad on a business trip.)
This isn't just a performance film. We need a story.
Would we be able to film it in one day?
That's my biggest concern.
(The music video of BLACKPINK's "GO")
She did the music video of aespa's "Armageddon."
She also worked with ALLDAY PROJECT.
She has to be the most famous director for dance films.
Jun Hui had her phone number.
I know Director Yoon Seung Rim.
- Who?
- I know Director Seung Rim.
- We'd like to work with you.
- Yes.
We already came up with the story.
So we called her right away.
At first, she said no. So Tae Woo called her.
It was like trying to win over Zhuge Liang...
by persuading her repeatedly.
But we managed to get her on our team,
and we can't wait to work with her.
I think the quality of our film will be much higher...
than theirs.
In the story we're picturing,
they have to face two moments of despair.
- Okay.
- The first moment will be...
after the battle.
The second moment will be after getting injured.
My chapter is all about setting up the storyline.
When she faces another crisis, she'll be in despair.
With the support of her friends, she'll recover from her injury.
Then she'll unwrap the bandage,
dance with the bandage, and throw it away.
She and her friends will become one.
My chapter will play a critical role in leading the story...
into the third chapter.
My chapter might be slightly iffy.
Toward the end, it's mostly dancing.
The storyline mainly comes from the beginning of the film.
It's not just a group scene.
It's not a mega crew performance.
If the group dance is only highlighted in my chapter,
it won't leave a strong impression compared to the 1st 2 chapters.
I need to add more story elements to my chapter.
I do have an idea.
Do you know why water bottles are important to battlers?
That decides who goes first.
Whoever goes first has to dance right away without the chance...
to listen to the song.
Because the bottle decides who goes first,
the bottle cap is super important.
We could try to convey...
that it doesn't matter anymore in the end.
- I see.
- Going 1st or 2nd...
Or having the chance to listen to the song...
They don't need that kind of benefit to win the battles.
In the end, we'll be evaluated individually.
Now, it's an individual mission under the name of a team mission.
All that matters now is this pretense.
It's very important to figure out a way...
to make my chapter shine.
We're at the location.
Yaho.
- Yaho.
- Dangjin, yaho.
It used to be a prayer center. Why does it look so pretty?
It has a nice vibe to it. I like it.
As for the film location we wanted,
considering the development of the plot,
it couldn't be just bright or dark.
It had to be bright, but dark at the same time.
It needed cool, yet warm vibes.
Chapter Four needs that childlike mood.
It has to look...
youthful and bright in an open area. It has to look lively.
In the last chapter, they're going to be on a big field.
And they'll bond through dancing.
Everything will pay off then.
It will be better up there.
(It's full of lively vibes.)
We can make use of everything here.
Filming the second chapter here sounds good too.
Then we can't film the last chapter here.
If this is the angle for the last chapter,
- we could do this for my chapter.
- But...
- We need a wide-angle shot.
- Yes.
The dancers will be up there too.
- This would work for my chapter.
- But not the second chapter.
If we use this spot for the fourth chapter,
we don't have an option for the second chapter.
Would that be weird? The spot we saw from the entrance?
That doesn't look that interesting.
It didn't go smoothly.
We had different opinions for each chapter.
That was the obstacle we had.
I'm afraid that this might not be the best spot for our film.
It was too dark and looked too humble.
We need to keep...
exploring more locations until we're satisfied.
(The 4-person team decided on their final location.)
It's not a place you'd find in real life.
It reminds me of "Alice in Wonderland."
I was shocked by the scale of it.
It was exactly what we were looking for.
We'd be able to film a lot of interesting scenes.
(The last production meeting for the 3-person team)
All three of our chapters look cool.
Our overall plot is amazing.
You never know. They might start crying all of a sudden.
- They're great dancers.
- Yes.
But they're still kids.
- It might not look real or cool.
- Right.
That did cross my mind.
The girl who we wanted for the lead role...
She said she couldn't do it because of the pressure.
She wanted someone else to take the role.
We decided that we wanted Yurichika for the lead role.
Yurichika.
Have you ever tried acting before?
I was in second grade.
I performed in a musical.
So I tried acting before.
We might need you to portray different kinds of emotions.
Do you think you can do it?
Yes.
I love your smile.
- She has a pure and innocent smile.
- Yes.
She's got it all.
Could we ask her...
to act angry?
(She starts acting on the spot.)
(Winning over the uncles already)
(Frowning fiercely)
(She's perfect to take the lead role.)
In my chapter,
she has to convey to the audience she's in despair.
Facial expressions are going to play an important role.
I'd like to explain the story.
(Explain the story?)
You'll be sitting at a table at the beginning of the story.
Because you're angry, you're going to break the table leg.
In the end, you and your friends...
will happily dance together.
That's the story.
What's wrong?
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Was I too scary?
I've done musicals.
But I've never done plays.
I've never done real acting.
She cried,
so I was worried about her.
The pressure was too much for me.
You needed to start practicing soon.
Didn't you feel like you didn't have enough time?
That wasn't important.
She was crying.
I told her it was okay.
I told her she could just learn the moves.
Great. At first...
I asked her if she didn't mind learning the choreography.
(She calmed down little by little while learning the choreography.)
I told her to think about it if the role was too much for her...
and let me know what she wanted to do later.
(Yurichika decided to try out for the main character.)
At first, it was a lot of pressure.
But now, I'm quite confident.
That's interesting.
I thought she'd be happy.
But it was overwhelming for her.
She must've felt a lot of pressure because she had to lead...
the story with her acting.
I thought we should...
try harder to communicate with her.
That crossed my mind.
My top priority is that...
these kids can complete the shoot without getting hurt.
I'll do my best...
and take care of them as their director.
All right. Let's try this.
(The 3-person team starts practicing for Chapter 3 in earnest.)
(Today's teacher, Kasper)
(When he jumps, )
(the kids jump too.)
(Papa Koo also jumps.)
To make this look hip,
we're going to try it with a jacket.
(Trying on the padded jacket to make it look hip)
What do you think?
It looks great.
Really?
It does look great.
(Koo Young also puts on the jacket.)
(He's getting excited.)
(Papa Koo is especially swift today.)
What was that?
I just almost slipped.
(Chuckling)
(I want to try it too.)
(He's funny.)
Ever since you put on the jacket,
you suddenly...
- look tough.
- My facial expression...
with this jacket...
(Suddenly feeling confident)
I can't seem to keep my head up straight.
I keep doing this.
(The magical, confidence-boosting jacket)
It's definitely light.
So it's easier to dance with the jacket on.
It's a good jacket to put on while dancing.
It makes the choreography...
look cool.
(Making his choreography hip)
This definitely makes me look cool.
Check out the zippers.
- It's got two zippers.
- Yes.
You can style the jacket however you want then.
It looks stylish.
(Papa Koo is excited now that he looks cool.)
(Jumping with excitement)
(Grooving just like Koo Young)
It's much more stylish.
It's light and warm. I like it.
It must be a new version.
I don't want to take it off.
(It's right up his alley.)
- Let's practice with the jacket on.
- Okay.
Let's do this.
- Let's go!
(Fully charged and ready for battle)
(Back to practicing)
(His confidence level is maxed out.)
(Their practice is going smoothly.)
(The 4-person team is warming up.)
- Isn't it light?
- Yes.
I feel light.
And the jacket feels light too.
It's a great color too.
It looks great on me.
MIN JUN. Look.
The two-way zipper looks great. Try it.
- I see. Like this?
- Yes. That's it.
Like this?
- Like this?
- Yes. MIN JUN.
We can style the jacket however we want.
I can easily practice with the jacket on.
- I can do this.
- And this too.
- It looks super hip.
- Exactly.
(They practice wearing the hip jacket.)
(Wearing a smile too)
(Their dancing is full of confidence.)
Faster!
(The 4-person team finishes practicing too.)
(The day of the filming)
This is crazy, seriously.
This is crazy.
You look so cute. Oh, my.
(Beaming eyes)
(Ta-da)
(Their defense is down.)
- You look so cute.
- So cute.
We cast the perfect girl for the role.
Our film is going to rock.
(They start off with Chapter 1, directed by INGYOO.)
In this chapter, ShiN exudes...
this timid vibe.
She has her role models...
and wants to be like them.
It's the start of the story.
Since not a lot of dancers will be in my chapter,
I tried to think of many ways...
to leave a strong impression.
Do you want to try this instead?
Do the same steps.
(The version with regular steps)
Let's try that while you make a turn.
(The version with turns)
Keep it smooth and relaxed.
(Making it look effortless)
Perfect.
Do you not like it?
Are you not happy with it?
She's not happy with it. Let's try one more time.
Quickly.
Things got seriously delayed.
It was delayed even from INGYOO's chapter.
This was the order of our shoot.
INGYOO's chapter,
my chapter,
Simeez's chapter, and MIN JUN's chapter.
He was supposed to take that long.
We had to film fast.
The weather affected my scene the most.
I was worried that the sun would go down soon.
There's already an hour and a half delay.
Despite the delay, INGYOO tried to work on the details.
Let's play it again, so the kids can watch it.
(Isn't this great?)
I didn't want to force the kids.
That will only make them cry.
At this rate, we're going to...
run into a problem.
I was thinking,
"Remember that this is an individual match too."
"This is risky."
We need to film my chapter first.
Looking at the weather, it would be dark by the time...
- BADA finishes hers.
- That makes sense.
They changed the order.
There's a two-hour delay.
I need to film mine quickly then.
I was a bit embarrassed.
Please pay attention, so I can only go over this once.
It was the last chapter of our story.
It's the closing segment.
I wanted to do the group dance.
My gosh. It's hot.
They're already tired.
The kids completely lost focus.
Given the size of the group,
I needed an assistant...
to film a dance video.
Sorry to ask this, INGYOO. Could you go up there...
and do what I say?
(INGYOO: Simeez's assistant)
- Here?
- INGYOO.
Move the podium, so they can step on it.
- Okay.
Get on the podium.
A little more.
I want Ra On to stand where you are.
Okay.
Send Eun Seo there.
Could you mark their spots with tape?
INGYOO, help those 30 dancers find their spots.
Group of 30 dancers. Please come on out.
INGYOO, can you get them to stand more closely?
- Stand more closely.
- Okay.
Hinowa, move half a step.
(Interpreting)
That's the spot.
It's great.
- Looks great.
- We're ready.
- Let's go.
- Here we go.
- Five...
(INGYOO is counting down too.)
She must've felt anxious.
I thought...
I should get their energy level up and hype them up.
(The captain of the cheer squad for Super Kids)
The kids are struggling in the heat.
- This is hitting them hard. Yes.
- Are they that exhausted?
I have no choice, though.
This is tough. We're colleagues.
But we're also competitors.
I'm at a disadvantage because we changed the order.
I'm very worried about their energy level.
I was upset.
(The shoot of the 3-person team)
(Back Koo Young starts filming first.)
Not to fall behind the schedule,
- Seven, eight.
- we had to secure several scenes.
Yurichika did a great job keeping up with the choreography.
She's such a good dancer.
There's no problem with the choreography, right?
(Nodding)
Yurichika.
Are you okay playing the main character?
I kept speaking Japanese to her.
I wanted to save time on interpretation.
I was able to make jokes...
in Japanese to Japanese kids.
Should I say I was able to break down the barrier?
There's so much to convey in Chapter Two.
I had a secret weapon.
I was confident.
I thought Koo Young's story was too difficult to understand...
and it wasn't audience-friendly.
She said she didn't know what it was about.
I think I can do a better job than Koo Young.
- But why did you mess up?
- Me?
- Mr. Back Koo Young was too good.
- Right.
- He was so good.
- This one.
(They watched Episode 1.)
By the way,
- why do you always look down?
- Right.
(Kasper staring at the floor in Episode 1)
If you glared like this,
you could've gotten one more vote.
Then it might not have been 9 to 0.
(They're driving me crazy.)
Chapter Three is about the group dance.
It's the only chapter with everyone dancing together.
I wanted to show the audience...
that even Kids Dancer can pull off an amazing performance like this.
So...
It might have been difficult for the kids,
but we needed to make sure everyone danced in sync.
Kids, the location of the water bottles has to match.
Again.
Seven. Stop.
Let's try again.
Seven, eight.
(Who got it wrong?)
(You?)
(Again)
(Only you guys will try again.)
(Let's try again.)
Since they're only kids, he talked to them nicely.
- "Again."
- But he sounded scarier.
(Re-do Ghost)
(They perfectly film the water bottle part.)
I was very satisfied.
It was a lot of fun, and we wrapped it up well.
I wasn't worried.
I was very confident.
One, two!
(Simeez's Chapter 4 shoot enters its final stretch.)
When shooting Simeez's chapter, I thought there would be light rain.
(Heavy rain)
Okay!
Goodness.
The children's energy...
Our part is in trouble.
They would really want to go home.
They were all soaked.
Even their shoes were wet.
What is he going to do? He's going last.
I had to work with the children at the end...
when their energy levels would be the lowest.
I think I felt sensitive and upset.
I can see everyone seated.
Try it. You can do it.
Five, six, seven, eight, one...
Chapter Two...
is about battle, the beginning of the conflict.
It's the most powerful part of the film.
I put a lot of effort into every shot...
so it could convey energetic...
and powerful moves.
I also want my part to be the kick of the film.
You can tell from the children's faces.
They were totally dazed.
I wasn't sure if their energy levels could handle it.
I was very anxious.
I really don't want to go to the Last Stage.
That could be my driving force.
But it feels devastating and disappointing.
It's tough.
My strength...
is my uniqueness.
The new paradigm I want to introduce...
uses cinematic directing techniques.
The main character is in panic because the mask fell off,
and his breath needs to stop.
I want that to be delivered to the audience as well.
I could tell from their faces that we couldn't go on like that.
So I tried to move on as long as I was okay with the takes.
Well done!
Good job!
(NOL Festival: A chance to see the Top 4 perform and teach classes)
(For more details, please check the NOL app.)
Is it already 1pm? Time is flying.
Back Koo Young.
What's that?
- BABYZOO.
- What is that?
(A special message that crossed borders)
How cute.
Hello. I'm Niuniu.
I got back home safely.
Thank you for creating...
such an amazing choreography...
that brought out our strengths.
I think...
you're very cool...
and charismatic when you dance.
I've improved so much thanks to your classes.
Thank you for putting so much thought...
into the choreography for the main character.
I really enjoyed...
getting to talk with you...
on the last day of filming.
(A proud dad smile)
You brought us so much joy...
with your unique choreography and classes.
Thank you for complimenting my waacking.
Would you like to do it alone, Rikka?
Seven, eight!
(No problem)
I'll work hard to get even better.
I didn't know who Kasper was at first.
So I looked up the preview.
You were scary.
(Laughing)
- Did you see me?
- Yes.
Was I very scary?
Yes.
I went there feeling really nervous.
But you were very nice and fun.
(Kasper's talent show)
Thank you...
for playing with us even during break time.
Who told you to cheat at such a young age?
(A surprise birthday party for Honatsu)
(Happy...)
(birthday)
I was very surprised...
when you wished me a happy birthday.
I still have the squishy and treasure it.
- Thank you, Kasper!
The experiences I had...
in Korea...
were all new,
but I enjoyed it because I made lots of new friends.
I want to dance together...
and be on stage with the teachers.
I'll work hard...
to become a better dancer...
so I can dance with you someday.
Thank you for teaching me.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
How cute.
Bye. See you again.
I love you. Thank you.
See you again.
How cute.
(Cute...)
They all got home safely.
They really worked hard.
I'm really...
grateful.
I still have this on my wallpaper.
It's a picture I took myself.
I feel really bad that I couldn't buy Honatsu soy-marinated crab.
He really wanted to try it.
I want to try soy-marinated crab.
He's asking you to buy him soy-marinated crab.
Okay.
I'm definitely going to buy soy-marinated crab for Honatsu.
Hi, I'm Kasper.
I feel awkward filming such a message.
I really loved...
spending time with you all.
There were many scenes I had only imagined.
But I was able to make them come true...
thanks to the Kids Dancers.
So I want to thank you once again,
and say you really worked hard.
I hope this film will be something you're proud of...
when you see it later.
I'm not sure if we'll be able to meet when you're older,
but I hope we can work on another great project together someday.
Don't get sick, eat well,
study hard,
and listen to your parents.
I miss you.
I love you.
BADA.
(The kids' heartfelt messages reach the 4-member team as well.)
(Smiling automatically)
(What is this?)
I got home safely!
Hello! I got back to Japan safely!
(He's cute.)
They filmed this at home?
Thank you for taking such good care of us and teaching us.
You're a really cute person.
You're like a Barbie doll in a movie.
(She's touched.)
You taught us house dance in our first class.
I wasn't familiar with the house style before,
but you really taught us well.
It was difficult because it was a new genre,
but you taught us everything patiently and kindly.
Thank you so much.
You're a very stylish person.
I think your choreography is really cool.
You're good-looking.
(Me?)
Our freestyle was really in sync.
I had so much fun.
I was able to enjoy freestyle dance...
thanks to you.
One, two, three, four.
Nice!
(That's right!)
(Smiling)
You played with me in the practice room every day.
I had so much fun.
(JEONG MIN JUN)
Your humorous teaching style...
kept us laughing throughout the practices,
and we were able to finish the project while having fun.
I really love your dance.
She's wearing glasses.
You're especially great at dancing.
You're really cool.
Your choreography...
helped me discover...
a different side of myself.
One, two, three!
Thank you for helping me...
practice each part...
until I could do it right.
I remember you getting us a bundle of snacks.
I was really happy.
And bacon potato.
Okay.
(I guess snacks really are the best.)
I'm so happy...
I got to take part in Super Kids Direct Mission...
and create something together with all of you.
I had so much fun,
and it was an experience unlike anything I'd had before.
It was really nice.
Thank you for the letter you wrote me.
I wanted to give the children a cute memory,
so I bought some four-leaf clover keychains.
Each leaf represents the four of us.
I'll always carry this keychain as a symbol of good luck.
They're so cute.
I really want to dance with you again.
Let's make sure to meet again.
I want to thank you once again.
Thank you for teaching me.
I hope to see you again.
Thank you.
I love you.
Bye.
They're cute.
How cute.
This is what it feels like.
It's like the kids I taught in kindergarten...
just graduated.
This is so nice. My heart feels warm.
I found an oasis...
in this dry, desert-like place.
This reminded me...
what it means to be a teacher again.
As a teacher...
They worked so hard and I'm so grateful.
So no matter how this ends,
I hope they don't get shaken...
by the strength of the time we spent together.
Hello.
This cold atmosphere.
The results day.
(Sighing)
Today is the day the results are announced.
My hands keep sweating.
We can watch the other team's final version.
I was curious to see...
what they did.
It's hard to predict.
But Koo Young would have added his storytelling punch.
We focused a lot...
on the dancing itself...
and kept things simple and pure.
But the other team...
I don't think it'll be easy to understand intuitively.
I think I'll have to read the synopsis...
to really understand it.
This is always so hard.
This is hard.
I've been to so many battles.
I've been to hundreds of them.
But still...
I'm really curious to see...
how the judges will evaluate and react to it.
Wouldn't we score highly in terms of completeness?
I don't think they'll even remember...
the other team's film.
In terms of the quality of the dance film,
our team also did really well.
It's the first time...
we're being given specific rankings and scores.
I really want to win. Seriously.
I hope we get recognized.
The goal of our film is to convey a narrative.
I think the one with a narrative...
likely received a higher score.
Why aren't you setting out the chairs?
- The chairs?
- The chairs.
(Announcing the result of Title Sequence Film Mission)
(There were chairs on the day of Artist Direct Mission)
Shouldn't there be chairs no matter what?
(Super Kids Direct Mission)
(Surprised)
- Here it is.
What?
(Super Kids Direct Mission)
"Super Kids Direct Mission. The judging begins."
"Stay in your Directors' Room."
(I see.)
I have to stay here. Not go there.
What? Why do I have to stay?
What does that mean?
"The judging begins." Now?
Do the judges come to my room?
What?
They're bringing the chairs in.
There are three chairs.
What?
(No way.)
Are the judges coming?
Why? What?
They're bringing the judges' chairs in.
(Those chairs look familiar.)
Are the real judges coming in now?
What?
We stay here, and the judges will watch us?
With this clear glass?
In front of my eyes?
Then we're waiting for the result here?
Gosh, unbelievable.
(What is this?)
(Shouting)
(BADA passes out.)
Is this how it's going to be done?
I really didn't expect this.
It's...
There's a sense of stability.
Because I'm with these three.
(Losing his mind)
I feel unsettled.
Why are you doing this?
(What's going on?)
(Gosh)
Seriously.
What kind of judges will be here?
Like... Parents?
Who will come?
This is really new.
(She spots them.)
Hello.
(He sees them too.)
They're here. Who are they?
- It's the judges.
- It's Honey J.
(Special judges, Shim Jae Won, Monika, Honey J)
- Gosh.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Hello.
It's Monika and Honey J.
- I can see them like this.
- Hi.
Hello.
Gosh. It's really intimidating.
Jae Won is here.
It's Jae Won.
- It looks like she's trapped.
- What's this?
They're being held captive.
Let me out.
They're like animals trapped in a zoo.
Is this right?
- By the way...
- Can you hear us?
I can't.
It's intimidating.
Jae Won judges videos incredibly well.
My mouth is bone-dry.
"Kids Direct."
Because we're mothers.
I have an immense interest...
- in kids' dance.
- You'll...
- Totally.
- look at them with mother's heart.
How will Honey J judge with a mother's heart?
The two of them are mothers.
(Sighing)
What kind of assessment will they give?
We have to watch this while trapped in this room.
In real-time.
I think...
kid dancers are practically a cheat code.
Is there anyone who wouldn't like Super Kids?
No.
There is neither animosity nor resistance.
They need to deliver a performance...
worthy of a "cheat code" to generate explosive impact.
Failing to direct effectively is a significant drawback.
Teams and individuals should be evaluated based on..
- the director's capabilities.
- Right.
We have to evaluate that.
The judges don't know who directed what.
It is completely anonymous.
It is fair for the judges to evaluate us...
anonymously.
Team evaluation. Individual evaluation.
I am definitely confident in team evaluation.
But I can't afford to let our guard down.
This is an individual match.
It'll be a hard fight.
I have to be completely different.
I don't want to go to the Last Stage this time.
I want to watch from the second floor.
- Shall we see?
- "See?"
- Wait.
- I have to watch.
(I have to watch their reaction.)
(Standing up)
This is a prime spot.
I'm excited.
(Start by watching the 4-person film video)
(Nervous)
(Chapped lips)
(The Mask: Be Yourself)
There's the synopsis.
(Synopsis)
(Characters)
(Chapters)
(Chapter 1, The Mask, Chapter 2, The Battle)
(Chapter 3, The Truth, Chapter 4, The New Generation)
- Cute.
Look at their acting.
Cute.
"Are you okay?"
They're all cute.
My chapter is the part...
where they gain superpowers through the mask.
As soon as she puts on the mask, she starts dancing.
Yes.
The judges have to be surprised by their dancing.
Good!
If ShiN had come to us, we could've made it even more impressive.
This mask is crazy.
Gosh.
Awesome popping.
The reaction here is important.
I hope it works.
They said wow.
It worked, INGYOO.
Transition.
- It's a battle.
- Next up is BADA's part.
BADA is nervous.
Their spinning is excellent,
so they can't help but cheer.
The kids are good.
- Here's the kids' dance.
- It's Xunxun.
Kids wearing masks and kids not wearing masks...
are battling each other.
Kids wearing masks are much more confident.
"Do you want to try it on too?"
"I think it's awesome."
Kids wearing masks aren't scared.
They're showing their stuff.
The mask came off by mistake.
Now it's MIN JUN's chapter.
The ear is broken.
- Oh, no. The ear is broken.
- She realizes that it's broken.
It intensifies.
A dark horde appears.
They have to be wowed here.
See? I told you they'd be wowed.
I think this part is really cool.
This part is good.
They filmed it well like a martial arts movie.
It worked, MIN JUN.
They demonstrated through a blast of energy...
that they could dance even without masks.
Their reaction is really good.
It's Qiuqiu.
They'll be wowed here.
The transition is good.
"I can dance with confidence without a mask."
(I have to hand it to them here.)
Monika's reaction is surprisingly positive.
Everyone merges together.
Have they become one?
"We can do it without a mask."
"We can all do well without it."
Let's go.
They're so good.
Cute.
They're pleased.
The reaction here is important.
This part is good.
Simeez's chapter is so pretty.
Jack. B is definitely good.
The innocence and happy vibes that only kids can provide.
He's mature.
Cute.
- Are you okay?
"Are you okay?"
Was it all in their imagination?
(What?)
We make a surprise appearance at the end.
I look too funny.
That drives me crazy.
Is that how they appear?
The four directors gave them the mask.
(Laughing)
(The production crew laughs.)
Why are you laughing?
(Cringe)
I think it's a bit funny.
Is it because their expression looks awkward?
(Watch the full video of Super Kids Direct Mission...)
(on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
The reaction isn't bad.
They cheered.
Jae Won is nodding.
I think they're starting the evaluation.
I'm so curious.
What are they saying?
I want to know.
(Screaming)
What are they talking about?
I think they're talking about something funny.
I liked that street dance was authentically reflected.
Yes. Right.
It's great how each of the kid dancers effectively...
showcases their own strengths.
The downside is that the same types of dancers were repeatedly used.
They keep overlapping.
The patterns the dancers use to showcase...
their specialties are all the same.
Jingjing keeps popping.
They do the b-boying.
All the four directors...
directed the super kids dancers.
They were too greedy.
They needed to compromise, but they didn't.
It's both an individual competition and a team competition.
Right.
From a judge's perspective,
I was scrambling to keep up...
right from the first impression.
- I see.
- I was scrambling.
Using the mask as an object was good.
I wish it had been a little more straightforward.
Right. That was confusing for me as well.
I don't think the before-and-after was clear...
when they put on the mask.
I don't think the message that they're good without the mask...
came across clearly.
The only way...
to express that was through the children's expressions...
and eyes...
in this film. It's supposed to be, "I can dance well."
When the camera moves, another kid goes, "I can dance well too."
It wasn't straightforward.
I think it was a loose end in the story.
I don't think I found anything special.
I just thought, "The children were good."
They're good!
Why are they all so cute?
They're so cute.
All I said was, "The children are cute, and they dance well."
Even aside from the synopsis,
there isn't anything that really leaves a lasting impression.
That's a bit disappointing.
I think Chapter One ended after setting up the story.
I liked that it showed a dancer who carried the theme throughout,
but it couldn't overcome the limitations of the opening.
There needs to be a strong impact in each section.
It lacked impact.
That's when I was worried.
I might end up in the Last Stage.
Chapter Two was the easiest.
It told the story through a battle.
That could have been the smart move.
But the concepts overlap a bit.
The concepts for Chapter 2 and Chapter 3.
Chapter 2 and Chapter 3 were all about battling.
BADA's chapter had so many overlapping parts.
If the overlapping parts...
had more impact, that's fine.
But honestly,
I think it lacked impact compared to the other chapters.
I think they're talking about what was lacking.
I kept feeling that something was wrong.
But Chapter Three...
had a very trendy filming style,
so there was quite a lot to see.
When it comes to the cinematography, variety, and events,
Chapter Three did well.
I also think Chapter Three had a nice overall structure.
I think the judges' reaction to my part...
were actually much better than I expected.
Usually, you'd think...
that if you place first on your team,
you're less likely to end up in the Last Stage.
I think it does make me a little hopeful.
I think Chapter Four...
was about the characters coming together.
The kids were so happy dancing in the rain.
I almost cried. It looked like the ending.
Qiuqiu's ending part...
was like a sports drink commercial. It was fun.
The pure, happy vibe that only kids can bring.
I wanted that vibe to come through.
But in the last part,
that water show was a bit questionable.
I wasn't sure why there was rain.
It was like a device to build up to the climax.
When you think something is a good piece of work,
you don't really have to ask, "Why?" You just have exclamations.
In terms of storytelling,
I kept asking, "Why?" right up until the end.
(Why is there suddenly water?)
(Why is she suddenly falling?)
(Why are they suddenly saying, "Are you okay?")
Why did it change to these kids?
What does it mean?
I had to keep searching for the meaning. That's disappointing.
I couldn't understand.
We definitely won the team battle.
It's time to shock the world.
There were some parts that were similar to ours.
BADA and Koo Young's battle scene.
Kasper and I also had...
the same narrative about overcoming and resolving challenges.
MIN JUN and Simeez both used water.
I'm curious to see how these things will be shown.
Okay!
It's starting.
("ONWARD" Synopsis Character lineup:)
(Main and supporting characters, 30 kids dancers, child cameo)
(Chapter 1: "Stuck")
(Chapter 2: "The Temperature of a Gaze")
(Chapter 3: "Back to Play")
That's pretty. This is fun.
I like the beginning.
That's crazy.
It starts off really strong.
That's right.
It's so cool.
I incorporated every genre...
into the Super Kids' battle scene.
Nice!
Show them, Niuniu!
That's crazy.
Niuniu did some breaking.
This scene is great.
We made a hip-hop crew and showed the hip-hop moves.
They're so good.
We brought out the freestyle.
That was a good shot.
In such a small space, they made it so fun.
The visuals are insane.
That's right. This is how it's supposed to be.
This is fun. It was really filmed well.
Let's go, Yurichika! We'll show them!
They clapped.
It's fun.
They're reflecting on the mistakes from the past battle.
It's what Jae Won likes.
It's on a whole different level.
Overcome it!
Yurichika practicing with determination.
Let's go, Yurichika!
She's so cool!
She did so well.
She's really amazing.
Again!
That's so cool!
She injured his leg while practicing too hard.
(She's constantly impressed.)
Good. It's working.
Kasper's part.
The child gets discouraged.
You can understand it.
His shadow is moving separately. That's insane!
It's giving me chills.
This is so sophisticated.
We have a good composition.
Goodness, this is so cool.
The difference in perspective.
The way she looks at the person she admires.
Her friends still dance well.
When she looks up...
She's still there, unable to do anything,
but they keep dancing.
It's so interesting how the children are sitting on the stairs.
Then, for the first time, she notices...
that there are others who admire him.
This is legendary.
She performs while removing the bandage.
The choreography is fun!
At the end, she throws away her bandage.
This is going to work.
Please, my chapter.
They have great teamwork.
All the directing is connected.
Amazing!
Yurichika overcame it!
This is giving me chills.
She succeeded!
This is amazing.
Let's go!
They're good!
This part is nice!
In my chapter, I wanted to highlight the group choreography.
Nice.
It's crazy.
The last part!
This is so my style.
Now, the last part.
I wanted to deliver a message in my chapter.
Goodness. What's going on?
Goodness!
This is the next generation.
In the end, the water bottle falls down,
and a baby dances out of joy.
That's how the scene ends.
Dancing is what you do when you're in joy.
That's the message I wanted to deliver.
That was so cool.
This is how it's supposed to be.
(He's touched.)
Actually, I think it's the most high-quality film...
that was produced in this show so far.
It's shocking.
The work of the three feels like one cohesive piece.
Yes. It was one cohesive piece.
They worked as a team.
The same object appeared in each chapter.
That connection.
I liked...
how cohesive it felt.
It felt like the clear bottle...
came from the rule...
that dancers commonly use.
A water bottle is a very symbolic object for dancers...
that decides the order of battles.
The water bottle takes Yurichika back...
to memories of the battle.
It was used as a device.
In Chapter Three, the water bottle serves as a symbol...
of passing dreams on to the next generation.
It's so fun how they end by spraying water.
It connects because they're using water bottles.
When you think about what you'd film...
with the Kids Dancers,
this is something beyond expectations.
I'm so jealous,
and it warms my heart.
The previous one...
really showcased the kids' skills.
Here, the director's direction really carried them through.
Chapter One was really sophisticated.
There were so many unique transitions.
There were so many iconic scenes.
However, battles...
are quite easy to express.
It's a structure we've seen many times before.
It's quite predictable.
Koo Young's part...
wasn't one with explosive moments.
My chapter...
doesn't incorporate...
as much dance as the other chapters do.
In that sense,
judging by the judges' reactions,
my chapter made me feel the most nervous.
There are more symbolic scenes...
in Chapter Two.
He took the highlight in the middle.
I think it flowed smoothly to Chapter Three.
I like it because it's something I haven't seen before.
I think the bandage part came out nicely.
They reacted as soon as they saw it.
There might be a chance.
I was hopeful.
In Chapter Three,
the message that comes through is really touching.
The children help her get back up.
I was teary.
As for Chapter Three,
it had group choreography,
so there wasn't anything special.
I thought it was ordinary.
I could say many things,
but as for this team,
the three directors did a good job, but the production team...
really understood their ideas well.
That makes it more amazing.
Hold on.
What production team was it?
Yoon Seung Rim produced it.
It was Rigend Film.
The fact that they were able to get him on board...
- proves their ability as well.
- That's right.
This decision created that piece in the end.
That played a big part.
Directing is about making decisions.
Knowing talented people is also an ability in this industry.
That's right.
Recruiting a producer?
That's also a director's ability.
You can't argue with that.
We had to bring a professional production team on board...
because we had to capture both the quality of the video...
and the ideas behind it.
That requires professional people.
(After the 3-person team's film was revealed)
That's so cruel.
Why am I crying so much? This is crazy.
I was really devastated.
When their film was played...
It wasn't like I didn't know the field.
I could have done more,
like putting a team together for them.
I felt devastated.
It broke my heart.
(Film evaluation ends)
The Super Kids Direct Mission...
with the Kids Dancers ended.
Well done.
- Well done.
- This was really...
We worked so hard.
You completed a piece...
as a team in this mission.
However, it's an individual competition...
where survival depends...
on each director's directing skills.
The final score...
is based on the combined scores...
from the team evaluation and individual chapter evaluation.
Choreographers on the same team...
receive the same score for the overall film evaluation,
but their final rankings may differ...
depending on their individual chapter scores,
which assess their directing abilities.
Today, only three...
of the seven directors will survive,
while the remaining four...
will advance to the Last Stage: 24H,
their final chance...
to stay in Street World Fighter: Directors' War.
(Sighing)
Four out of the seven?
It's not even three.
If half of the seven will be going there,
I could be one of them.
I felt so uneasy.
Going to the Last Stage didn't make sense.
I was expecting to go even further.
It doesn't make sense.
Now,
the team evaluation results...
will be revealed.
(Super Kids Direct Mission, Team Evaluation)
Based on the judges' reactions alone,
we have a chance in the team score.
There were reactions on the explosive parts,
but it wasn't that much.
Team Back Koo Young, BABYZOO, and Kasper's score...
for kids' character development...
and utilization of the dancers...
will be revealed.
Yurichika seemed to be the main character.
If one person leads the storytelling,
it allows you to fully immerse yourself in that character,
so I think it could have been a good choice.
Compared to the other team, we had a main character.
So if it felt like the other kids' characters didn't come through...
What am I going to do?
The score...
will be revealed.
(Kids' Character Development and Dancer Utilization: 95)
95 points.
(He's startled.)
That's a very high score.
We did it.
I was very happy.
I was very happy. We should have...
at least ten points more than the other team.
We could have 95 and they could have 85.
That meant...
we had a perfect score.
We were able to show all 11 characters well.
In this section,
I think we could get a higher score.
We did a good job of incorporating each child's individual skills...
into the performance.
We just have to hope our narrative...
resonates with the judges and lands with them.
Then will the score...
of Team BADA, Simeez, INGYOO, and MIN JUN...
be higher than 95?
Their score...
will be revealed now.
(Kids' Character Development and Dancer Utilization: 90)
95 points versus 90 points. My goodness.
I was expecting a higher score.
The reaction was a little underwhelming.
I thought we might be in trouble.
If we couldn't get a higher score in that...
I don't feel good about it.
I don't think...
they really needed to use the mask...
as an object.
But the mask serves a role...
- The role.
- in telling the story.
But it would have made sense...
by following the characters without the masks.
One dancer...
The girl kid dancer was the leading story.
I think it's a little disappointing...
that they put so much meaning into the mask.
The three-person team's film...
takes us, the viewers, along...
- through one main character.
- Yes.
That makes it easy.
- I kept saying it was intuitive.
- Right.
It was easy to watch.
I think it was smart to choose to tell the story...
- from one person's perspective.
- Right.
It was really smart.
The two teams...
are currently five points apart.
I was worried. It was only 5 out of 100 points,
but it felt really big.
There was a five-point difference here,
but I thought the gap would widen more...
in the next criteria.
In terms of completeness.
Now,
the total team evaluation score...
including the Dance Film Quality score will be revealed.
Our team has to get a higher score.
That's for the sake of my survival,
but I also want...
the piece I worked on to do well.
We made an overall...
cohesive piece.
So I think we'd get a high score...
in terms of film quality.
The judges reacted well too.
(They gave endless cheers for the 3-person team.)
(Glancing)
Nothing has ever gone...
as expected.
So I couldn't stop feeling nervous.
The total team evaluation scores...
will be revealed.
(Taking a deep breath)
(Super Kids Direct Mission, Team Evaluation)
The 3-person team got 195 points.
The 4-person team got 165 points.
(Exclaiming)
(Feelings satisfied)
(Great work)
Great work.
I was really happy.
That was only natural.
Our idea came across well.
We won.
I was really happy.
I thought we could really win by a landslide,
just like I hoped.
The Dance Film Quality score for the three-person team...
was 100 points.
The work of the three...
feels like one cohesive piece.
Yes. It was one cohesive piece.
They worked as a team.
You can feel everything the child is going through...
, from their struggles with dance...
to the process of overcoming them.
So even though the story is divided into chapters,
it made me think that maybe it's all one story.
When the baby came out,
I was like, "Are we starting all over again?"
(The film ended.)
Isn't this Chapter Two?
I think the directors really talked a lot with each other.
In the previous film,
they did their best as choreographers.
Here, they did their best as directors.
- As directors.
- They really...
I'll give 100 points for film quality.
- I'll totally give them 100 points.
- I'll give them 100 points as well.
A hundred out of a hundred points.
It's not easy to get 100 points.
Our strategy to make...
one cohesive film...
worked really well.
The two teams are just 40 points apart.
I think I lost all my energy.
I feel stressed.
My hair is falling.
Thirty points?
That could be dangerous.
To keep all of us safe,
we needed to be in a more secure position.
I had that thought.
The team with a better score...
in the team evaluations for Super Kids Direct Mission...
is the three-person team.
Now, we have the individual chapter evaluation,
which will determine each director's fate.
(Super Kids Direct Mission, final Evaluation Results)
Even within the same team,
the final rankings can change completely...
depending on the individual chapter evaluation results.
Since the team score carries less weight...
than the individual chapter score,
the individual evaluation is more important in the end.
It's too early to relax.
We're leading in the team evaluations,
but things could turn around.
So I felt nervous.
First, the director who received the highest score...
in the three-person team...
will be revealed.
Based on the judges' reactions alone,
BABYZOO's part got the biggest reaction.
(Explosive cheers)
(Watching proudly)
Kasper's part.
The choreography using the bandages was so cool.
The concept was fully explained.
Kasper has a chance.
The three-person team.
Here is the director...
with the highest score.
Why is this so tense?
Since when did my hands get so sweaty?
I have to win.
This is an individual match.
I want to get the highest individual score...
and enter the semifinal safely.
The director with the highest score in the three-person team is...
Kasper with a score of 491.
I was surprised. It made me proud.
(Well done.)
Kasper deserves to take first place.
He got the perfect score.
- What?
- It's 100 out of 100.
There were symbolic scenes.
I also liked how he used the bandage.
He got injured,
so he danced with a bandage on.
That was pretty innovative.
The way he used the bandage.
It was new.
I also liked the choreography.
He's very smart.
- He didn't miss a single thing.
- That's what I mean.
Every scene is worth keeping.
That's a relief.
It's relieving.
It got rid of all that frustration...
that had been building up since I joined this show.
(Lost by 9 to 0)
(I wanted to hide.)
(Kasper even had to do the Last Stage: 24H.)
(It's too brutal.)
(Hash and Renan from my first team...)
(also did the Last Stage.)
(I teamed up with MIN JUN this time.)
(Kasper the guide to the Last Stage)
(All that frustration...)
(Being 1st in the team felt relieving.)
Today,
I was evaluated solely on my film.
I competed anonymously.
So it means a lot.
It's true victory.
I'm delighted to win that way.
To me,
Kasper was perfect.
Today, he's not a key ring guy.
He's a perfect winner.
Then which director received the highest score...
in the four-person team?
I hope my strength do its part...
in the individual score.
If I end up doing the Last Stage again,
it means every Last Stage.
It'll be a new record in the history of this series.
I don't want to end up doing it.
If I lose, I have no chance...
of avoiding the Last Stage.
I must win no matter what.
There is a high chance it could be me.
(Dizzy)
Do I have to fight with my all...
and return from the Last Stage?
Or just go home?
I want to avoid the Last Stage at all cost.
I'm counting on the individual score.
Here is the result for the four-person team.
(Who received the highest score in the 4-person team?)
(JEONG MIN JUN placed 1st in the 4-person team.)
It felt great.
Being first means...
I'm getting further away from the Last Stage.
It looks like I have a chance.
(Well done!)
It was a shame,
but I saw that coming.
I noticed that the judges liked MIN JUN's a lot.
(Cheering)
This is good.
Good job.
Hey.
I like the transition.
Chapter Three's music is my favorite.
Based on the videos,
Chapter Three is the simplest,
- isn't it?
- Yes, it's nice.
There was nothing...
that I didn't like.
It's a relief.
It felt like my direction was approved. I was happy.
The final result of Super Kids Direct Mission.
The director with the highest score in the three-person team is...
Kasper.
And in the four-person team is...
JEONG MIN JUN.
Now, what matters is Director JEONG MIN JUN's ranking...
who placed first in the four-person team.
If JEONG MIN JUN got higher...
than Back Koo Young and BABYZOO in the three-person team,
he'll get to avoid the Last Stage...
and enter straight to the semifinal.
However, if he didn't beat their scores,
his chance to head to the Last Stage increases.
I don't want to end up in the Last Stage this time.
Even if our team is leading,
that might turn things around.
I was anxious.
I hoped the 3 of us made the top 3.
But you never know.
I was worried about BABYZOO and Back Koo Young's parts...
receiving lower than expected.
(Please.)
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
I'm getting anxious.
(Glancing)
Kasper was more anxious about it.
- Tae Woo, don't worry.
- What?
Don't worry.
Although I said that, I couldn't get the umbrellas out of my head.
It's time to check the other five people's results.
Where will these five people rank...
with what score?
And...
where will JEONG MIN JUN who got the highest score...
in the four-person team...
rank?
Who will get to advance directly to the semifinal?
And who will head to the Last Stage?
Last Stage? Never.
Avoid it if possible.
I want to enter the semifinal.
The result of the Super Kids Direct Mission...
that will determine the seven directors' fate.
Here it is.
I was just scared.
I was afraid of checking the result.
My hands didn't stop sweating.
I was nervous.
I don't know. But I am nervous.
I'm very nervous.
- This is crazy.
- I must survive.
Please.
(2nd, 3rd, 1st)
(The 3-person team made the top 3.)
We placed 1st, 2nd, and 3rd.
(1st place, Kasper)
(2nd place, Back Koo Young)
(3rd place, BABYZOO)
My goal was...
win together or lose together.
It meant a lot.
- Good job.
- Gosh.
- Well done.
Good job.
We complimented each other and held hands.
Everyone's hands were sweaty.
(How can this happen?)
That shows how nervous we were.
Sorry and thank you.
Thank you.
I couldn't be more proud.
I couldn't thank the kids enough.
Rather than feeling relieved for surviving,
I was proud of Kasper and BABYZOO...
who worked so hard.
I didn't see that coming at all.
My ranking was most surprising.
Honestly, I was expecting fifth.
Kasper and I are only one point apart.
BABYZOO and I are only two points apart.
I received such a high score that made my ranking pointless.
I'm honored.
(On the other hand, )
(the 4-person team is determined to join the Last Stage.)
- Oh, my gosh.
- Everyone is...
on the train to the Last Stage.
I was devastated.
(Absurd)
I didn't think this could happen.
On top of that, I placed seventh.
I've never ranked that before.
It felt like watching a bad nightmare.
(INGYOO got to choose the team when his concept paper placed 1st.)
(He was triumphant in the past.)
(The most regrettable chapter was...)
(INGYOO's.)
(The color didn't really match.)
(INGYOO wasn't prepared enough.)
(It was boring.)
(INGYOO's name was mentioned for lack of directing skills.)
(During the judges' evaluation)
(This video focuses on explaining the main character.)
(It seems they wanted a safe start.)
(This person could've done something...)
(to show the energy.)
(I understand this person had to explain the story, )
(so there's less dancing.)
(The film drew my attention...)
(after the first half.)
(That didn't overcome the limitations of the opening.)
I was in despair.
I'm setting up a new record.
This is my third Last Stage.
It felt in vain.
Helpless before an overwhelming wall.
Now, directors who will be heading...
to the third Last Stage of Street World Fighter: Directors' War is...
JEONG MIN JUN, Simeez,
BADA, and INGYOO.
As a consequence,
only 2 will survive out of 4...
and go for the next mission.
The other two will be eliminated.
I'll have to do my best.
I have to overwhelm everyone.
I have the upper hand when it comes to the Last Stage.
That's my home ground.
I shall survive.
I don't care who's eliminated.
I'm going to survive no matter what.
Last Stage: 24H.
It begins now.
This is tragic.
It's finally starting.
I want to win desperately.
My brain is awake 24 hours.
I will come back again this time.
(We all have to do it.)
(The 4-person team enters the third Last Stage.)
(I can't imagine myself being on that stage.)
(It felt like watching a bad nightmare.)
(When I was told I had to do it for the third time...)
(Sighing)
(MIN JUN's done the Last Stage three times already.)
(Screaming)
(Angry punch)
(Including the 24 hours for the Last Stage...)
(72 hours)
(The train to Last Stage will set off.)
(The condition of the Last Stage: 24H)
(It is an umbrella.)
(When umbrellas meet lights and videos, )
(they become objects that create numerous scenes.)
(The most abstruse objects ever)
(This is driving me crazy.)
(Will this be done before today?)
(We'll project images onto an umbrella.)
(Let's paint them with petals.)
(The fact that I'm inside is the kick.)
(BADA's appearing from there?)
(The umbrella looks like a sword.)
(How about a ninja?)
(Ninja, sword)
(Mission)
(They're perfect for wings.)
(The umbrella is turned inside out.)
(For the last part, I was thinking about...)
(turning the umbrella inside out.)
(Light)
(As a three-timer of the Last Stage, )
(I'm going to survive this time no matter what.)
(I'll take the ticket to the semifinal.)
(This is fun. Our performance is most exciting.)
(No one can beat me.)
(Let's make it super cool.)
(It's more about...)
(looking cool than winning.)
One, two, three, four.
(I'll show them what I'm capable of.)
(Last Stage: 24H)
(I hate to lose anyone.)
(No one deserves to leave.)
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War Nationwide Concert Tour)
(Seoul from November 21 to 22)
(Gwangju on November 28)
(Busan on December 5)
(That's insane.)
(That's his trademark.)
(Anyway, it was the best. The best of the best.)
(The last stage before the semifinal)
(Who will be the two directors...)
(to have their names on the stage?)
(At this point, )
(the mistake will be critical.)
(Hey, you were great. What's wrong?)
(It's not just your fault.)
(It happened to us.)
(We did the best we could.)